[uplifting music]
[musik yang membangkitkan semangat]
[logo whistling]
[logo bersiul]
[bravo]
[bagus sekali]
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
[metallic noise]
[suara logam]
[air hissing]
[udara mendesis]
[waves crashing]
[ombak menghantam]
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
["You're Going Up In My Head" by Chet Baker and Paul Bley playing]
["You're Going Up In My Head" oleh Chet Baker dan Paul Bley dimainkan]
♪ You climb into my head ♪
♪ Kau merayap ke dalam kepalaku ♪
♪ And you remain as a disturbing chorus ♪
♪ Dan kau tetap menjadi paduan suara yang mengganggu ♪
♪ And I find you wandering around ♪
♪ Dan aku menemukanmu berkeliaran ♪
♪ In my brain ♪
♪ Di otakku ♪
♪ Like bubbles in a glass of champagne ♪
♪ Seperti gelembung dalam segelas sampanye ♪
[engine roaring]
[mesin menderu]
♪ You climb into my head ♪
♪ Kau merayap ke dalam kepalaku ♪
♪ Like a sip of foamy burgundy beer ♪
♪ Seperti seteguk bir merah anggur berbusa ♪
♪ And I find the mere mention of you ♪
♪ Dan aku menemukan hanya dengan menyebutmu ♪
♪ Like the kicker in a julep or two ♪
♪ Seperti minuman keras dalam satu atau dua julep ♪
[engine roaring]
[mesin menderu]
♪ The emotion of thought ♪
♪ Emosi pikiran ♪
♪ So that you can think of my plea ♪
♪ Agar kau bisa memikirkan permohonanku ♪
♪ Cast a spell on me ♪
♪ Berikan aku mantra ♪
♪ Still, I tell myself ♪
♪ Tetap saja, aku berkata pada diriku sendiri ♪
Are you ready to play?
Apakah Anda siap untuk bermain?
Yeah.
Ya.
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
[singing in foreign language]
[bernyanyi dalam bahasa asing]
[Upbeat music continues]
[Musik yang ceria terus berlanjut]
[guests chatting]
[tamu sedang mengobrol]
Bubbly?
Berbusa?
- Lover 650. - What is that?
- Kekasih 650. - Apa itu?
Oh.
Oh.
Fabulous scope, isn't it?
Cakupan yang luar biasa, bukan?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Baik. - Baik.
What do you think, honey?
Bagaimana menurutmu, sayang?
Let's have a drink and see what else they have.
Ayo minum dan lihat apa lagi yang mereka punya.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Oke. - Oke.
- Thank God.
- Terima kasih Tuhan.
[guests chatting]
[tamu sedang mengobrol]
Small, isn't it?
Kecil, bukan?
Here you go, madam. A glass of champagne.
Ini dia, Nyonya. Segelas sampanye.
Thank you so much.
Terima kasih banyak.
Does anyone else want something to drink?
Apakah ada lagi yang mau minum sesuatu?
Mmm.
Hmm.
I'm glad you're enjoying it, ma'am.
Saya senang Anda menikmatinya, Bu.
Allow me, sir.
Izinkan saya, Tuan.
- Oh thank you. - Pleasure.
- Oh, terima kasih. - Senang sekali.
It's a good day.
Ini hari yang baik.
There are a lot of excellent jets and luxury vehicles here.
Ada banyak jet dan kendaraan mewah yang bagus di sini.
Mmmm.
Hmm.
You know, these rich people like it.
Tahukah Anda, orang-orang kaya menyukainya.
likes to leave his keys in the
suka meninggalkan kuncinya di
consoles for anyone to take with them.
konsol yang dapat dibawa oleh siapa saja.
Very interesting.
Sangat menarik.
I didn't know.
Saya tidak tahu.
[Upbeat music continues]
[Musik yang ceria terus berlanjut]
- [Amy laughs] - So what's going on?
- [Amy tertawa] - Jadi apa yang terjadi?
Then there is caviar and champagne.
Lalu ada kaviar dan sampanye.
- [laughs] Oh, I love this. - [Amy laughing]
- [tertawa] Oh, aku suka ini. - [Amy tertawa]
Continue.
Melanjutkan.
Well then I guess
Baiklah kalau begitu kukira
We will eventually have to pack up
Kita akhirnya harus berkemas
our things and head to our own private island.
barang-barang kami dan menuju pulau pribadi kami.
Ah, yes, the one at the fishing pier.
Ah, ya, yang di dermaga pemancingan.
No, no, honey. The other one.
Tidak, tidak, Sayang. Yang satunya.
The one in the garden.
Yang ada di taman.
Oh, the herb garden.
Oh, kebun herbal.
Yes, the herb garden.
Ya, kebun herbal.
- Yes Yes. - It has strawberries.
- Ya Ya. - Ada stroberi.
Yes, strawberries.
Ya, stroberi.
Why are we still here?
Kenapa kita masih disini?
- Let's go. - [man] Mr. Carson.
- Ayo berangkat. - [pria] Tuan Carson.
Ah, Mr. Perez.
Ah, Tuan Perez.
It's a pleasure to see you in person.
Senang bertemu Anda secara langsung.
And first I wanted
Dan pertama-tama aku ingin
thank you for inviting us.
terima kasih telah mengundang kami.
And also tell you that my
Dan juga memberitahumu bahwa aku
My colleagues and I are very happy.
Saya dan rekan-rekan saya sangat gembira.
Glad to hear it.
Senang mendengarnya.
- Yes, and this is my- - Wife.
- Ya, dan ini adalah- - Istriku.
- Wife. - Hello.
- Istri. - Halo.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- Halo. - Senang bertemu Anda.
Nice to meet you.
Senang berkenalan dengan Anda.
So you came all the way here to avoid checking the planes?
Jadi kamu datang jauh-jauh ke sini untuk menghindari pemeriksaan pesawat?
Oh well...
Baiklah...
The jets are very nice but to be honest,
Jet-jetnya sangat bagus tapi sejujurnya,
We're here to, well, see the collection.
Kami di sini untuk, ya, melihat koleksinya.
The collection. The car collection.
Koleksi. Koleksi mobil.
Oh. You've heard of that, huh?
Oh, Anda pernah mendengarnya, ya?
- Oh, yes, definitely. - Oh, yes, we have.
- Oh, ya, tentu saja. - Oh, ya, kami punya.
Is it possible?
Apakah mungkin?
What do you think?
Bagaimana menurutmu?
Well, I guess since you came here.
Baiklah, saya rasa sejak kamu datang ke sini.
-Ah. - Wonderful.
-Ah.- Luar biasa.
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
[Perez] Mr. Carson, ma'am, this is just
[Perez] Tuan Carson, Nyonya, ini hanya
a small selection from my private collection.
sebagian kecil dari koleksi pribadi saya.
- [Mason] Oh. - [door whistle]
- [Mason] Oh. - [peluit pintu]
I think the most demanding admirers of private jets
Saya pikir pengagum jet pribadi yang paling menuntut
They also tend to appreciate better cars.
Mereka juga cenderung menghargai mobil yang lebih baik.
Yes. Oh, look, honey, a Lamborghini.
Ya. Oh, lihat, sayang, sebuah Lamborghini.
[Amy] Oh.
[Amy] Ah, tidak.
Yes, this is the SVJ prototype.
Ya, ini adalah prototipe SVJ.
- Prototype? - Look!
- Prototipe? - Lihat!
It is the Mercedes SLR 722S Roadster.
Itu adalah Mercedes SLR 722S Roadster.
Mrs. Carson, I'm impressed. You know your vehicles.
Bu Carson, saya terkesan. Anda tahu kendaraan Anda.
- [Amy laughs] - Yes she does.
- [Amy tertawa] - Ya, dia melakukannya.
Of course, none of these are for sale.
Tentu saja, tidak ada satupun yang dijual.
- Bugatti. - [Amy] Oh.
Oh, ya.
[Mason] Yes.
[Tukang batu] Ya.
The Bugatti Veyron.
Bugatti Veyron.
Guess.
Tebakan.
Well, guess what, honey. Go ahead.
Baiklah, coba tebak, Sayang. Silakan saja.
Mmm, more than a million?
Mmm, lebih dari satu juta?
[Mason] More than a million.
[Mason] Lebih dari satu juta.
[laughs] Close, 2.5.
[tertawa] Dekat, 2,5.
- Oh my God. - Oh.
Ya Tuhan. - Oh.
[laughs] Well, it's a lovely collection.
[tertawa] Wah, itu koleksi yang indah.
It's true?
Benarkah?
Huh?
Hah?
You know, about the Pagani?
Tahukah Anda tentang Pagani?
Oh.
Oh.
Do you have it?
Apakah kamu memilikinya?
Let's find out, shall we?
Mari kita cari tahu, ya?
[Upbeat music continues]
[Musik yang ceria terus berlanjut]
-Ah. - [Perez laughing]
-Ah. - [Perez tertawa]
[Amy panting]
[Amy terengah-engah]
[Perez] This is priceless.
[Perez] Ini tak ternilai harganya.
This Saudi gentleman offered me 20 million.
Pria Saudi ini menawari saya 20 juta.
- [Mason] Really? - [Amy] Oh.
- [Mason] Benarkah? - [Amy] Oh.
[Pérez] I didn't take it, of course.
[Pérez] Tentu saja, saya tidak mengambilnya.
[Mason] Yeah.
[Mason] Ya, benar.
Well, can I ask you a personal question?
Baiklah, bolehkah saya mengajukan pertanyaan pribadi?
Have you ever driven these amazing machines?
Pernahkah Anda mengendarai mesin menakjubkan ini?
[Perez laughing]
[Perez tertawa]
Well, what about you?
Baiklah, bagaimana dengan Anda?
That would only cause its value to depreciate.
Itu hanya akan menyebabkan nilainya terdepresiasi.
Ah, I see, I see.
Ah, aku paham, aku paham.
[Perez] You know, I'm starting We lift them up
[Perez] Kau tahu, aku mulai Kami mengangkat mereka
from time to time to listen to its engine.
dari waktu ke waktu untuk mendengarkan mesinnya.
[Mason] Ah.
[Tukang Batu] Oh.
Would you two like to sit on it?
Apakah kalian berdua ingin duduk di atasnya?
- Could we? - I love that.
Bisakah kita? - Aku suka itu.
- [Amy gasps] - My heart is racing.
- [Amy terkesiap] - Jantungku berdebar kencang.
- How exciting! - Okay, yes, you could.
- Betapa menariknya! - Oke, ya, kau bisa.
- You want, yes, you want. - Yes!
- Kamu mau, ya, kamu mau. - Ya!
[Perez] I just can't believe I'm doing this.
[Perez] Saya tidak percaya saya melakukan ini.
- [Mason laughing] -Ah.
- [Mason tertawa] -Ah.
- You are very special. - Do you mind?
- Kamu sangat istimewa. - Kamu keberatan?
- Okay. - Go ahead.
- OK silahkan.
Let's see. Oh.
Mari kita lihat. Oh.
[Perez] Be careful.
[Perez] Hati-hati.
[Mason chuckles]
[Mason terkekeh]
Wow, yes.
Wah, tentu saja.
[doors slamming]
[pintu dibanting]
[Keyboard keys clicking]
[Klik tombol keyboard]
Communications out.
Komunikasi keluar.
Would you mind if we started the engine just so we could hear it?
Apakah Anda keberatan kalau kami menyalakan mesinnya supaya kami bisa mendengarnya?
- No, I...
- No I...
Of course. So just for a second?
Tentu saja. Jadi, tunggu sebentar?
Okay. Yes, thank you.
Oke. Ya, terima kasih.
[engine roaring]
[mesin menderu]
- Wow. - [Mason laughing]
- Wah. - [Mason tertawa]
- It feels good, doesn't it? - Yes Yes.
- Rasanya enak, bukan? - Ya Ya.
- Oh. - [engine revving]
- Oh. - [mesin menderu]
Okay, go ahead. You can turn it off now.
Oke, silakan. Anda dapat mematikannya sekarang.
- Go ahead and turn it off. - [engine revving]
- Silakan matikan saja. - [mesin menyala]
[Mason] I can't hear you.
[Mason] Aku tidak bisa mendengarmu.
I said you can turn off the ignition.
Kataku, kau bisa mematikan kunci kontaknya.
- [engine revving] - I can't hear you.
- [mesin menderu] - Aku tak dapat mendengarmu.
- Fold over. Turn off the ignition. - [Mason] Hit him, Link.
- Lipat. Matikan kunci kontak. - [Mason] Pukul dia, Link.
Lights out. Starting now.
Mati lampu. Mulai sekarang.
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
♪ I don't know about you, but I feel good ♪
♪ Aku tidak tahu tentangmu, tapi aku merasa baik ♪
[fist bumps]
[berbenturan tinju]
♪ I don't do it for you, but I feel good ♪
♪ Aku tidak melakukannya untukmu, tapi aku merasa senang ♪
- Mr. Carson, can you...? - [engine revving]
- Tuan Carson, bisakah Anda...? - [mesin menyala]
Get down on the ground. Get down, dammit.
Turunlah ke tanah. Turunlah, sialan.
Down now! Get down.
Turun sekarang! Turun.
♪ You stop, you drop, baby, then you roll ♪
♪ Kau berhenti, kau jatuh, sayang, lalu kau berguling ♪
♪ You twerk, you pop, booty so swollen ♪
♪ Kamu bergoyang, kamu bergoyang, bokongmu bengkak sekali ♪
♪ I would hate myself too if I were you ♪
♪ Aku juga akan membenci diriku sendiri jika aku jadi kamu ♪
♪ And when it comes to business, I say two ♪
♪ Dan jika menyangkut bisnis, aku bilang dua ♪
[Amy] 10 seconds, guys. 10 seconds.
[Amy] 10 detik, teman-teman. 10 detik.
- We're rolling. - [engine revving]
- Kami melaju. - [mesin menyala]
♪ I have my pocket full of hundred dollar bills ♪
♪ Kantongku penuh dengan uang seratus dolar ♪
- [engine roaring] - [tires squealing]
- [mesin menderu] - [ban berdecit]
♪ Two shots, I'm running ♪
♪ Dua tembakan, aku berlari ♪
♪ Two and I'm dazzling tonight ♪
♪ Dua dan aku mempesona malam ini ♪
[engine roaring]
[mesin menderu]
Oh. I just have a feeling.
Oh, aku hanya punya firasat.
which one would you take?
kamu akan ambil yang mana?
Ah, I'll go for the Bugatti, don't worry.
Ah, saya akan pilih Bugatti, jangan khawatir.
Oh man, that's so 2000.
Waduh, itu tahun 2000 sekali.
Motherfuckers, stay eating cement, okay?
Orang-orang brengsek, teruslah makan semen, oke?
Hector, take the keys.
Hector, ambil kuncinya.
♪ Oh yeah, I love it, it's okay ♪
♪ Oh ya, aku menyukainya, tidak apa-apa ♪
♪ It's okay ♪
♪ Tidak apa-apa ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, I'm drinking the bottle ♪
♪ Ya, ya, aku minum botolnya ♪
- ♪ Let go ♪ - ♪ Hang out with supermodels ♪
- ♪ Lepaskan ♪ - ♪ Nongkrong bareng supermodel ♪
- ♪ Let go ♪ - ♪ Feel like I won the lottery ♪
- ♪ Lepaskan ♪ - ♪ Merasa seperti aku memenangkan lotre ♪
♪ I don't know about you, but I feel good ♪
♪ Aku tidak tahu tentangmu, tapi aku merasa baik ♪
- [engine revving] - [upbeat music continues]
- [mesin menderu] - [musik ceria terus berlanjut]
[Mason] Link, How do we see each other?
[Mason] Link, Bagaimana kita melihat satu sama lain?
Just in time.
Tepat pada waktunya.
- Ah! [laughing] - [engine roaring]
- Ah! [tertawa] - [mesin menderu]
♪ I don't know about you, but I feel good ♪
♪ Aku tidak tahu tentangmu, tapi aku merasa baik ♪
That was fun, huh?
Itu menyenangkan, ya?
Yes, putting The Ritz.
Ya, menempatkan The Ritz.
- Yes. - Yes.
- Baik. - Baik.
That's all, honey.
Itu saja, sayang.
It's over. No more.
Sudah berakhir. Tak ada lagi.
Now it's just you and me.
Sekarang hanya ada kamu dan aku.
We can go to our island.
Kita bisa pergi ke pulau kita.
Our fishing pier, strawberries.
Dermaga pemancingan kami, stroberi.
Yeah.
Ya.
- Are you excited? - Yes.
- Apakah kamu bersemangat? - Ya.
What's happening?
Apa yang terjadi?
Nothing.
Tidak ada apa-apa.
No no.
Tidak, tidak.
- Uh, I know that look. - You're wrong, aren't you?
- Uh, aku tahu ekspresi itu. - Kau salah, bukan?
I'm not trying to spoil any parades here, but
Saya tidak mencoba merusak parade apa pun di sini, tapi
I am detecting unusual activity at the exit point.
Saya mendeteksi aktivitas yang tidak biasa di titik keluar.
- [anxious music] - What?
- [musik cemas] - Apa?
Well, what kind of unusual activity, Link?
Nah, kegiatan yang tidak biasa seperti apa, Link?
[Link] We have company.
[Link] Kami punya perusahaan.
We have a helicopter and it is not licensed.
Kami memiliki helikopter dan tidak berlisensi.
[Helicopter blades thud loudly]
[Suara baling-baling helikopter terdengar keras]
- [uncomfortable music] - That's the FBI.
- [musik yang tidak nyaman] - Itu FBI.
That's the FBI.
Itu FBI.
Shit, huh...
Sial, ya...
It doesn't look very good.
Kelihatannya tidak bagus.
Several vehicles block you there.
Beberapa kendaraan menghalangi Anda di sana.
- Good. - Mason.
- Bagus. - Mason.
No, Anton has this. Don't worry about it.
Tidak, Anton punya ini. Jangan khawatir.
I know him.
Saya kenal dia.
[tense music]
[musik tegang]
[sirens wailing]
[suara sirene meraung]
[Helicopter blades thud loudly]
[Suara baling-baling helikopter terdengar keras]
Mason.
Tukang batu.
No, Anton will take care of this, I promise.
Tidak, Anton akan mengurus ini, aku janji.
- [anxious music] - [sirens blaring]
- [musik yang membuat cemas] - [suara sirene meraung]
Let's take these boys for a quick spin, Shawn.
Ayo kita bawa anak-anak ini jalan-jalan sebentar, Shawn.
[Shawn chuckles]
[Shawn terkekeh]
[sirens wailing]
[suara sirene meraung]
[tense music]
[musik tegang]
- [Shawn laughing] - Are you ready?
- [Shawn tertawa] - Apakah kamu siap?
Here we go.
Ini dia.
[sirens wailing]
[suara sirene meraung]
-[vehicles crushed]-[booming explosion]
-[kendaraan hancur]-[ledakan dahsyat]
Oh!
Oh!
-[glass breaking]-[Shawn cheering]
-[kaca pecah]-[Shawn bersorak]
[Shawn] Oh my God!
[Shawn] Ya Tuhan!
[Anxious music]
[Musik yang mencemaskan]
[Officer] Hold position.
[Petugas] Tahan posisi.
See this.
Lihat ini.
[Officer] Wow, wow, wow!
[Petugas] Wow, wow, wow!
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Ayo, ayo, ayo, ayo!
- [tense music] - [Shawn] Oh, no!
- [musik menegangkan] - [Shawn] Oh, tidak!
Curse!
Menyumpahi!
-[gun booming]-[Shawn cheering]
-[suara tembakan]-[Shawn bersorak]
[siren blaring]
[suara sirene berbunyi]
How did they know?
Bagaimana mereka tahu?
How would the fucking FBI know?
Bagaimana FBI sialan itu bisa tahu?
- What are you putting...? - [gun cocking]
- Apa yang kau taruh...? - [menekan pistol]
[Anxious music]
[Musik yang mencemaskan]
[mumbles indistinctly]
[bergumam tidak jelas]
How long?
Berapa lama?
- Two years? - Yes.
- Dua tahun? - Ya.
- Really? - UH Huh.
- Benarkah? - UH Huh.
You could have caught me at any time.
Kau bisa menangkapku kapan saja.
I never had the proper evidence before.
Saya tidak pernah memiliki bukti yang tepat sebelumnya.
- Is this okay? - UH Huh.
- Apakah ini oke? - UH Huh.
- [radio silence] - [Link] Mason, are you there?
- [keheningan radio] - [Tautan] Mason, apakah kamu di sana?
- Yes. - Mason, are we going to plan B?
- Ya. - Mason, apakah kita akan menggunakan rencana B?
Don't do it, Mason.
Jangan lakukan itu, Mason.
- So it's all just- - Yeah.
- Jadi itu semua hanya- - Ya.
All this time.
Selama ini.
[tense music]
[musik tegang]
[Helicopter blades thud loudly]
[Suara baling-baling helikopter terdengar keras]
[Anton] Man, this helicopter is on this bitch.
[Anton] Wah, helikopternya ada di atas wanita ini.
What's up, boss?
Ada apa, bos?
Wow, you were good.
Wah, hebat sekali kamu.
You were...
Kamu adalah...
How professional.
Betapa profesionalnya.
I bought it hook line and sinker.
Saya membelinya secara utuh.
[Link] Mason, are you there?
[Link] Mason, apakah kamu di sana?
- It's over. - It's okay.
- Sudah berakhir. - Tidak apa-apa.
Well, you'll have to tighten the
Baiklah, kamu harus mengencangkannya
trigger, because I will not leave my team.
pemicu, karena saya tidak akan meninggalkan tim saya.
I am not.
Saya tidak.
We are doing plan B.
Kami sedang menjalankan rencana B.
Plan B is underway.
Rencana B sedang berjalan.
Shit.
Kotoran.
Let's go to plan B.
Ayo, kita ke rencana B.
Plan B? Plan B, okay, okay, okay.
Rencana B? Rencana B, oke, oke, oke.
- Plan B. - We have to go to plan B, bro.
- Rencana B. - Kita harus pergi ke rencana B, saudara.
We can't go to fucking plan B.
Kita tak bisa meneruskan rencana B.
Damn, this shit was going well.
Sial, semua ini berjalan dengan baik.
But we never did plan B.
Namun kami tidak pernah membuat rencana B.
Mason, you know, I'm not a great swimmer.
Mason, kau tahu, aku bukan perenang yang hebat.
- [siren wailing] - [anxious music]
- [suara sirene meraung] - [musik yang mencemaskan]
[sirens blaring]
[suara sirene meraung]
[Anton] Are you ready?
[Anton] Apakah kamu siap?
- [tense music] - [sirens wailing]
- [musik menegangkan] - [suara sirene meraung]
[engine acceleration]
[akselerasi mesin]
[both growling]
[keduanya menggeram]
[tires screeching]
[ban berdecit]
-[water splashing]-[both grunting]
-[percikan air]-[keduanya mendengus]
Plan B sucks.
Rencana B menyebalkan.
[water splashes]
[percikan air]
[siren whirring]
[suara sirene menderu]
[Police radio chatters]
[Obrolan radio polisi]
[Amy] I'm fine.
[Amy] Aku baik-baik saja.
I'm fine.
Saya baik-baik saja.
[Amy panting]
[Amy terengah-engah]
Thank you. Thank you.
Terima kasih. Terima kasih.
[Shawn growls]
[Shawn menggeram]
Come on, Mason, we have to go.
Ayo, Mason, kita harus pergi.
Link and Hector.
Link dan Hector.
They'll be here in a minute.
Mereka akan tiba sebentar lagi.
[police chattering]
[polisi berceloteh]
[engine roaring]
[mesin menderu]
Damn! I knew this was all fucked up.
Sial! Aku tahu ini semua kacau.
I can't believe it.
Aku tak dapat mempercayainya.
How do you think I feel?
Menurutmu bagaimana perasaanku?
I bought it.
Saya membelinya.
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
♪ Forever and ever, I love you so much ♪
♪ Selamanya dan selamanya, aku sangat mencintaimu ♪
♪ Forever and ever, I want to let you know ♪
♪ Selamanya dan selamanya, aku ingin memberitahumu ♪
♪ Just what you mean to me and all your charms ♪
♪ Apa yang kau maksudkan untukku dan semua pesonamu ♪
♪ You have that magic touch ♪
♪ Kamu punya sentuhan ajaib itu ♪
♪ A magical smile when you are near me ♪
♪ Senyuman ajaib saat kau di dekatku ♪
Shawn.
Shawn, siapa yang tidak kenal Shawn?
What the hell are you doing here?
Apa yang sedang kamu lakukan di sini?
You know, I was, uh, I was in the neighborhood.
Anda tahu, saya, eh, saya ada di lingkungan itu.
[Mason] Oh, yeah?
[Mason] Oh ya?
How have you been? I missed you.
Apa kabar? Aku kangen kamu.
Well.
Dengan baik.
Do you get anything?
Apakah kamu mengerti sesuatu?
Yes, some bass and some snapper.
Ya, beberapa ikan bass dan beberapa ikan kakap.
[Birds singing]
[Burung bernyanyi]
What kind of beer are you drinking?
Kamu minum bir jenis apa?
Now, you didn't come here to
Sekarang, kamu tidak datang ke sini untuk
ask me what kind of beer I'm drinking.
tanyakan padaku jenis bir apa yang sedang aku minum.
If you would check your messages from time to time.
Jika Anda mau memeriksa pesan Anda dari waktu ke waktu.
Well, I'd have to have a phone to do that, wouldn't I?
Yah, saya harus punya telepon untuk melakukan itu, bukan?
Here, hydrate yourself.
Sini, minumlah air putihmu.
[Mason sighs]
[Mason mendesah]
Well, what is it?
Baiklah, apa itu?
¿Mmm?
Hmm?
Look at you, you're a mess.
Lihat dirimu, kamu berantakan.
Yes, I agree with that comment.
Ya, saya setuju dengan komentar itu.
So?
Jadi?
I can't believe you let a woman do this to you.
Aku tidak percaya kau membiarkan seorang wanita melakukan ini padamu.
She broke you, man.
Dia menghancurkanmu, kawan.
Your lucky dad isn't here to see this.
Ayahmu yang beruntung tidak ada di sini untuk melihat ini.
You don't have to worry about me.
Anda tidak perlu khawatir tentang saya.
I'm living life.
Saya menjalani hidup.
Don't worry.
Jangan khawatir.
You are my brother.
Kamu adalah saudaraku.
Of course I care about you.
Tentu saja aku peduli padamu.
Okay, so what is it? What do you need?
Oke, jadi apa itu? Apa yang Anda butuhkan?
Scupel.
Memahat
¿Mmm?
Hmm?
Maybe he has another job lined up.
Mungkin dia punya pekerjaan lain.
[laughs] Oh, no, out of the question.
[tertawa] Oh, tidak, itu tidak mungkin.
You need to get back in the game, man.
Kamu harus kembali ke permainan, kawan.
Well, is it effective?
Nah, apakah efektif?
You know, I have something hidden. I'd give it to you.
Kau tahu, aku punya sesuatu yang tersembunyi. Aku akan memberikannya padamu.
Just tell me what-
Katakan saja padaku apa-
I can't watch you wither away like this.
Aku tidak tega melihatmu layu seperti ini.
We can't let him get away with this.
Kita tidak bisa membiarkan dia lolos begitu saja.
It's breaking my heart, okay?
Ini menghancurkan hatiku, oke?
We are the best team in the business.
Kami adalah tim terbaik dalam bisnis ini.
We have to go back there.
Kita harus kembali ke sana.
We can't do it without you.
Kami tidak dapat melakukannya tanpa Anda.
You need to get back to work.
Anda harus kembali bekerja.
That's what Dad would say if he were still here.
Itulah yang akan Ayah katakan seandainya dia masih di sini.
Dad?
Ayah?
Dad died in an orange jumpsuit.
Ayah meninggal mengenakan baju oranye.
Old, broken, alone.
Tua, rusak, sendirian.
No no no no no.
Tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak.
I prefer fishing.
Saya lebih suka memancing.
What's up with the team?
Ada apa dengan tim?
Anton has a daughter to put into school.
Anton memiliki seorang putri yang harus disekolahkan.
Link is drowning in crazy debt.
Link terlilit hutang yang gila-gilaan.
Where are you going?
Kamu mau pergi ke mana?
We all knew the risks.
Kita semua tahu risikonya.
At the sea.
Di laut.
..the tide has come in. - [Shawn] Here. - [phone ringing]
..air pasang telah datang. - [Shawn] Di sini. - [telepon berdering]
In case you change your mind.
Jika Anda berubah pikiran.
Don't worry, it's untraceable.
Jangan khawatir, itu tidak dapat dilacak.
[Decker] The bodies were never found in Miami.
[Decker] Mayatnya tidak pernah ditemukan di Miami.
It's out there somewhere.
Itu ada di suatu tempat di luar sana.
He means nothing to me.
Dia tak berarti apa-apa bagiku.
It was a mistake, okay?
Itu sebuah kesalahan, oke?
What if I told you that we picked up white conversations in Mason's group?
Bagaimana jika saya katakan bahwa kami mendengar percakapan orang kulit putih di kelompok Mason?
Do you think they are planning something?
Apakah menurut Anda mereka sedang merencanakan sesuatu?
[Birds singing]
[Burung bernyanyi]
[phone ringing]
[telepon berdering]
[Mason groans]
[Mason mengerang]
I told you I'm not interested.
Sudah kubilang aku tidak tertarik.
[Link] Ugh, you sound rude.
[Link] Ugh, kamu terdengar kasar.
All good?
Semuanya baik?
Link.
Link.
Ey.
Mata.
[clears throat] What's wrong?
[berdeham] Ada apa?
[Link laughs] That's cute.
[Link tertawa] Lucu sekali.
You're a funny guy.
Kamu orang yang lucu.
Wait.
Tunggu.
Shawn didn't tell you?
Shawn tidak memberitahumu?
Tell me what?
Katakan padaku apa?
[Link] Oh, shit.
[Link] Oh, sial.
That bad?
Seburuk itu?
[Link] It's putting your butt on a plane.
[Link] Itu seperti menaruh pantat Anda di dalam pesawat.
Oh God.
Ya Tuhan.
[Mason growls]
[Mason menggeram]
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
[Mason groans]
[Mason mengerang]
[Mason sighs]
[Mason mendesah]
[Upbeat music continues]
[Musik yang ceria terus berlanjut]
[happy funk music]
[musik funk yang ceria]
[honk]
[membunyikan]
[The upbeat funk music continues]
[Musik funk yang ceria terus berlanjut]
♪ You are so far away ♪
♪ Kamu begitu jauh ♪
♪ Like a bright light shining through the cloudy sky ♪
♪ Seperti cahaya terang yang bersinar melalui langit berawan ♪
♪ I can feel it too ♪
♪ Aku juga bisa merasakannya ♪
[The upbeat funk music continues]
[Musik funk yang ceria terus berlanjut]
Do we know each other?
Apakah kita saling mengenal?
I'm gonna need your finger.
Aku butuh jarimu.
Not that one, your thumb.
Bukan yang itu, ibu jarimu.
I'm waiting for the joke.
Saya menunggu leluconnya.
You know that place you manage?
Anda tahu tempat yang Anda kelola?
I'll need your help to steal it.
Aku butuh bantuanmu untuk mencurinya.
[laughs] Oh, you can't be serious.
[tertawa] Oh, Anda tidak mungkin serius.
I'm serious.
Saya serius.
And my crew too.
Dan kru saya juga.
They are inside, ready to shoot everyone in the
Mereka ada di dalam, siap menembak semua orang di dalam
bank unless you do exactly what I tell you.
bank kecuali Anda melakukan apa yang saya perintahkan.
So either you give me your thumb or I'll take it.
Jadi berikanlah jempolmu padaku atau aku yang mengambilnya.
[inhales slowly]
[menarik napas perlahan]
[dramatic music]
[musik dramatis]
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
Seriously, Shawn?
Serius, Shawn?
You're late. I thought you'd be here sooner.
Kamu terlambat. Kupikir kamu akan sampai lebih cepat.
Stop looking around, hide your gun and who is it?
Berhenti melihat-lihat, sembunyikan senjatamu dan siapa itu?
He is the director of the bank.
Dia adalah direktur bank.
- Oh God. - Don't worry.
- Ya Tuhan. - Jangan khawatir.
It's easy, it's cut and dried.
Gampang, mudah saja.
If it looks cut and dry, it isn't.
Jika kelihatannya jelas dan mudah dipahami, kenyataannya tidak.
Look, I came to you first, you said no.
Lihat, aku datang kepadamu lebih dulu, kamu bilang tidak.
What am I supposed to do?
Apa yang harus saya lakukan?
You brought the crew here, didn't you?
Kau bawa krunya ke sini, kan?
- Yes. - Okay, where are they?
- Ya. - Baiklah, di mana mereka?
They are inside.
Mereka ada di dalam.
Look, you can still change this.
Lihat, Anda masih bisa mengubah ini.
- I won't say anything, I swear. - Liar.
- Aku tak akan mengatakan apa pun, sumpah. - Pembohong.
Well, we're probably being watched by 14 cameras right now.
Yah, mungkin saat ini kita sedang diawasi oleh 14 kamera.
Do you have a plan B?
Apakah Anda punya rencana B?
I don't need a plan B when plan A is so good.
Saya tidak memerlukan rencana B ketika rencana A begitu bagus.
Well, that's all, that's all.
Baiklah, itu saja, itu saja.
Okay. This is the plan.
Oke. Ini rencananya.
You and Mr. Manager will wait
Anda dan Tuan Manajer akan menunggu
outside while I go find the team.
di luar sementara aku pergi mencari tim.
That?
Itu?
Just because it's my plan and not yours, is it bad?
Hanya karena itu rencanaku dan bukan rencanamu, apakah itu buruk?
Stop. It is not debatable.
Berhenti. Itu tidak bisa diperdebatkan.
Stay here.
Tetaplah di sini.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
[Suspenseful music builds]
[Musik menegangkan mulai terbentuk]
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
I thought you were holding him back.
Aku pikir kamu menahannya.
I tried it. Do you know how to put it?
Saya sudah mencobanya. Apakah Anda tahu cara mengatakannya?
Yeah, and why did you let it get that far?
Ya, dan mengapa Anda membiarkannya sampai sejauh itu?
First, I didn't let it get that far. It just happened.
Pertama, saya tidak membiarkannya sampai sejauh itu. Itu terjadi begitu saja.
And second, I was waiting for you to stop him.
Dan kedua, aku menunggumu menghentikannya.
Yeah, well, let's fix this right now.
Baiklah, mari kita perbaiki ini sekarang juga.
There is no reason why you and
Tidak ada alasan mengapa Anda dan
Anton should go down with my idiot brother.
Anton harusnya ikut turun bersama saudaraku yang idiot itu.
[Link] It may be too late.
[Link] Mungkin sudah terlambat.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
You really should listen to your friend.
Kamu seharusnya mendengarkan temanmu.
Trying to stop you from doing something really stupid.
Mencoba menghentikanmu melakukan sesuatu yang sangat bodoh.
Yeah, yeah, whatever, bro.
Ya, ya, terserahlah, Bung.
Just use your damn thumb.
Gunakan saja ibu jarimu.
Let's go.
Ayo pergi.
[alarm sounds]
[suara alarm]
Sorry, I forgot about retinol.
Maaf, saya lupa tentang retinol.
Hands in the air!
Angkat tangan!
- Calm down bro. - [gunshots]
- Tenanglah, bro. - [suara tembakan]
Ah!
Ah!
- [customers yelling] - I said hands in the air!
- [pelanggan berteriak] - Saya bilang angkat tangan!
[fist bumps]
[berbenturan tinju]
[officer grunting]
[petugas mendengus]
[arms roosters]
[senjata ayam jantan]
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[Hector] Fuck, leave it. Get down!
[Hector] Persetan, tinggalkan saja. Turun!
Get on the floor.
Turun ke lantai.
[Hector] Zip his ass up.
[Hector] Tutup ritsleting pantatnya.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
Hector, check the doors. No one is coming in or out.
Hector, periksa pintunya. Tidak ada yang masuk atau keluar.
[lock clicks]
[klik kunci]
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
Liaison, cameras. Anton, crowd control.
Penghubung, kamera. Anton, pengendalian massa.
Let's go. Let's go.
Ayo, ayo. Ayo.
[customer crying]
[pelanggan menangis]
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
Ah, fuck.
Ah, sial.
[customer crying]
[pelanggan menangis]
¡And! And! And!
Dan! Dan! Dan!
All right, everyone listen up. Eyes on me.
Baiklah, semuanya dengarkan. Perhatikan aku.
I didn't come here to play and I'm
Aku tidak datang ke sini untuk bermain dan aku
pretty sure i'm not lying.
cukup yakin aku tidak berbohong.
My name is Anton and that's my dog ​​Hec.
Namaku Anton dan itu anjingku Hec.
And we are the best of the best at what we do.
Dan kami adalah yang terbaik dari yang terbaik dalam apa yang kami lakukan.
Fucking piece of shit.
Bajingan sialan.
So if we all cooperate and act like
Jadi jika kita semua bekerja sama dan bertindak seperti
one team, this shit will be over in no time.
satu tim, masalah ini akan segera berakhir.
Heck, maybe you even have a good story to tell.
Ah, mungkin Anda bahkan punya cerita bagus untuk diceritakan.
Ma'am, I need you to sit down.
Nyonya, saya perlu Anda duduk.
I can't. I have back problems.
Aku tidak bisa. Aku punya masalah punggung.
Okay, ma'am. Let me help you.
Baiklah, Bu. Biar saya bantu.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
- You know what? - [pepper spray bubbling]
- Kau tahu apa? - [semprotan merica]
That was out of place.
Itu tidak pada tempatnya.
I understand you in a situation
Saya mengerti Anda dalam suatu situasi
complicated, but I'll let it pass.
rumit, tapi saya akan membiarkannya berlalu.
Miss Lady.
Nona, Nona.
[Grandma, sit down]
[Nenek, duduklah]
the suspenseful music fades out.
Musik yang menegangkan memudar.
Do this shit again. I'll kill you. Link, where are we?
Lakukan hal itu lagi. Aku akan membunuhmu. Link, di mana kita?
Getting dark in 3, 2, 1.
Menjadi gelap dalam 3, 2, 1.
[Intense music]
[Musik yang intens]
¡Mover!
Penggerak!
Wow, wow!
Wah, wah!
What part did you not understand, Shawn?
Bagian mana yang tidak kamu mengerti, Shawn?
I told you to stay outside.
Sudah kubilang padamu, tetaplah di luar.
And now what, what are we looking for?
Dan sekarang apa, apa yang kita cari?
I'm looking for a safe deposit box.
Saya sedang mencari kotak penyimpanan aman.
[Mason] One, two, how many?
[Mason] Satu, dua, berapa banyak?
[Shawn] Just one, that's all.
[Shawn] Hanya satu, itu saja.
But what's in it?
Tapi apa isinya?
A wallet.
Sebuah dompet.
- A wallet? A wallet. - A crypto wallet.
- Dompet? Dompet. - Dompet kripto.
I've been talking to you about cryptocurrencies forever.
Saya sudah lama berbicara kepada Anda tentang mata uang kripto.
Trust me. This is a big one.
Percayalah, ini masalah besar.
How big?
Seberapa besar?
[Shawn] The biggest one we've ever done.
[Shawn] Yang terbesar yang pernah kami lakukan.
[Intense music continues]
[Musik intens berlanjut]
Okay, come in.
Oke, masuk.
[Mr. Caras] Okay, I'm going, I'm going.
[Tuan Caras] Baiklah, saya pergi, saya pergi.
[Shawn] I'm looking for 1140.
[Shawn] Saya mencari 1140.
[Intense music continues]
[Musik intens berlanjut]
1140, we are looking for 1140.
1140, kami mencari 1140.
Come on. Help us.
Ayo. Bantu kami.
I'm looking. I- This is not my apartment.
Aku sedang mencari. A-Ini bukan apartemenku.
I don't know.
Aku tidak tahu.
[typing keys]
[mengetik tombol]
Come on, go, go!
Ayo, maju, maju!
[Intense music continues]
[Musik intens berlanjut]
- 1140. - Good.
- 1140. - Baik.
Let's open it. Come on, come on, guys.
Mari kita buka. Ayo, ayo, teman-teman.
Well, you have your keys, right?
Baiklah, kamu punya kuncinya, kan?
[Mason] ¿Shawn?
[Mason] Apa itu Shawn?
Why would I need another key?
Mengapa saya butuh kunci lainnya?
[Mr. Caras] You need two keys, mine and the owners'.
[Tuan Caras] Anda butuh dua kunci, kunci saya dan kunci pemilik.
Okay. Hey Link, where are you?
Oke. Hei Link, kamu di mana?
Link.
Link.
Could you bypass the safe?
Bisakah Anda melewati brankas itu?
- It's 1-1-4-0. - [Link] Working on it.
- Sekarang 1-1-4-0. - [Link] Sedang mengerjakannya.
I thought we weren't playing.
Aku pikir kita tidak sedang bermain.
I am, there is not, You need two keys.
Saya ada, tidak ada. Anda butuh dua kunci.
- I can't do anything about it. - How are we doing?
- Aku tak bisa berbuat apa-apa. - Bagaimana kabar kita?
[Link] We're almost there.
[Link] Kita hampir sampai.
[sirens blaring]
[suara sirene meraung]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
You seem pretty calm about this. Have you done this before?
Anda tampak cukup tenang dalam hal ini. Apakah Anda pernah melakukan ini sebelumnya?
Yes, sometimes. Four times to be exact.
Ya, kadang-kadang. Tepatnya empat kali.
Do you have any interesting stories?
Apakah Anda punya cerita menarik?
Not really, same ending.
Tidak juga, akhir ceritanya sama saja.
Same ending?
Akhir yang sama?
Cell. Some would-be robbers were shot dead.
Sel. Beberapa calon perampok ditembak mati.
About two years ago, in fact, a guy managed to get out
Sekitar dua tahun yang lalu, sebenarnya, seorang pria berhasil keluar
through the front door before he was shot.
melalui pintu depan sebelum dia ditembak.
[laughs] That was exciting.
[tertawa] Itu mengasyikkan.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[sirens blaring]
[suara sirene meraung]
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
[Officer 1] West side.
[Petugas 1] Sisi barat.
[garbled radio chatter]
[obrolan radio yang tidak jelas]
[Officer 2] Affirmative! Check it out.
[Petugas 2] Setuju! Coba lihat.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[Officer 1] To the west side, all the way.
[Petugas 1] Ke sisi barat, sepanjang jalan.
Boys in front, two men up.
Anak laki-laki di depan, dua pria di atas.
[Officer 3] Two subjects on the move!
[Petugas 3] Dua orang sedang bergerak!
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
Shawn, I have to ask you.
Shawn, aku ingin bertanya padamu.
What were you going to do without a second key?
Apa yang akan Anda lakukan tanpa kunci kedua?
I brought my drill.
Aku membawa borku.
Okay, well, that's fine. So what?
Baiklah, baiklah. Lalu bagaimana?
AND
DAN
they
mereka
..I learned about this special cobalt drill bit that drills through anything. And how did you learn how to do that on YouTube?
..Saya belajar tentang mata bor kobalt khusus yang dapat mengebor apa pun. Dan bagaimana Anda mempelajari cara melakukannya di YouTube?
Your entire search history is virtually
Seluruh riwayat pencarian Anda secara virtual
of public knowledge these days.
pengetahuan publik saat ini.
I had it on private mode.
Saya menggunakannya dalam mode pribadi.
No, there is no private mode, Shawn.
Tidak, tidak ada mode privat, Shawn.
[sigh] Okay, what else is in the bag?
[sigh] Oke, apa lagi yang ada di tas itu?
My stethoscope, my glasses, my C4, all my usual gear.
Stetoskop saya, kacamata saya, C4 saya, semua perlengkapan saya yang biasa.
- [suspenseful music] - [garbled chatter]
- [musik menegangkan] - [obrolan tak jelas]
[doors clicking]
[suara pintu berbunyi klik]
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
Well, what do you have?
Baiklah, apa yang kamu punya?
[Link] We have company.
[Link] Kami punya perusahaan.
Holy crap. They got here early.
Gila. Mereka sampai di sini lebih awal.
They are waiting for this.
Mereka sedang menunggu ini.
Okay, what else haven't you told me? Tell me everything.
Oke, apa lagi yang belum kau ceritakan padaku? Ceritakan semuanya padaku.
He did everything by the rules.
Dia melakukan segala sesuatunya sesuai aturan.
Well, they wouldn't be early.
Baiklah, mereka tidak akan datang lebih awal.
if you did everything by the rules.
jika Anda melakukan semuanya sesuai aturan.
Damn it, Shawn.
Sialan, Shawn.
You wipe that damn smile off your face.
Kau hapus senyum terkutuk itu dari wajahmu.
What else? Tell me, what else haven't you told me?
Apa lagi? Katakan padaku, apa lagi yang belum kau ceritakan padaku?
[Shawn] I did everything by the book.
[Shawn] Saya melakukan semuanya sesuai aturan.
Cancel code 1140.
Batalkan kode 1140.
- Here we go. - [security beeps]
- Di sini kita mulai. - [suara keamanan]
This better be a lot of damn crypto.
Ini pasti banyak sekali kripto.
Trust me. It will be worth it.
Percayalah padaku. Itu akan sepadan.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[box noise]
[suara kotak]
It looks like a small USB flash drive.
Bentuknya seperti flashdisk USB kecil.
What the fuck?
Apa-apaan ini?
Is this the correct box?
Apakah ini kotak yang benar?
Shit!
Kotoran!
Fuck, it's supposed to... Where the fuck is it?
Sial, seharusnya begitu... Di mana sih itu?
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[sirens blaring]
[suara sirene meraung]
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
Special Agent Decker, FBI.
Agen Khusus Decker, FBI.
This is a local situation. I did not request the FBI.
Ini situasi lokal. Saya tidak meminta FBI.
I've got it under control.
Aku bisa mengendalikannya.
It is a situation that involves criminals
Ini adalah situasi yang melibatkan penjahat
which top our most wanted list.
yang berada di posisi teratas dalam daftar orang paling dicari.
We haven't even identified anyone yet.
Kami bahkan belum mengidentifikasi siapa pun.
Where do you get this information?
Dari mana Anda mendapatkan informasi ini?
Look, I'm here to help.
Lihat, saya di sini untuk membantu.
- Help? - Mm-hmm.
- Tolong? - Mm-hmm.
In what way?
Dengan cara apa?
I am your negotiator.
Saya negosiator Anda.
UH no.
UH tidak.
If you want to look over your shoulder
Jika Anda ingin melihat dari balik bahu Anda
from my negotiator, you are more than welcome.
dari negosiator saya, Anda sangat diterima.
But I'm in charge here. I make the decisions.
Tapi saya yang bertanggung jawab di sini. Saya yang membuat keputusan.
You may want to check with your supervisor about this.
Anda mungkin ingin berkonsultasi dengan atasan Anda tentang hal ini.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Alright, where are we, team?
Baiklah, di mana kita, tim?
Ey.
Mata.
Yes, they just appeared.
Ya, mereka baru saja muncul.
Yeah.
Ya.
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
[Captain Fabrizio sighs]
[Kapten Fabrizio mendesah]
[garbled radio chatter]
[obrolan radio yang tidak jelas]
[latch clicks]
[klik kait]
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[suspenseful music fades out]
[musik menegangkan menghilang]
[Keys jingle]
[Gitar kunci]
I don't understand. This is the box.
Saya tidak mengerti. Ini kotaknya.
I'm supposed to be here!
Aku seharusnya ada di sini!
[Mason] Calm down.
[Mason] Tenanglah.
There... there is supposed to be a password and a wallet.
Di sana... seharusnya ada kata sandi dan dompet.
.. worth 600 million dollars. - Come here, come here.
..bernilai 600 juta dolar. - Kemari, kemari.
Come here. Come here.
Kemarilah. Kemarilah.
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
Saya akan menanyakan beberapa pertanyaan kepada Anda.
This is very important.
Ini sangat penting.
How did you find out about this box, this cryptography?
Bagaimana Anda mengetahui tentang kotak ini, kriptografi ini?
How do you think I found it?
Menurutmu bagaimana aku menemukannya?
I did my research, I did everything by the book.
Saya telah melakukan penelitian, saya melakukan segalanya sesuai aturan.
I did everything we always do.
Saya melakukan segala sesuatu yang selalu kami lakukan.
Who did this cryptocurrency belong to?
Milik siapakah mata uang kripto ini?
Yes, some lady, some like a crazy rich society lady.
Ya, beberapa wanita, beberapa seperti wanita dari kalangan masyarakat kaya raya.
Well, do you remember his name?
Baiklah, apakah Anda ingat namanya?
Pharaoh, Pharaoh, Elizabeth Pharaoh.
Firaun, Firaun, Elizabeth Firaun.
Elizabeth Pharaoh.
Elizabeth Firaun.
Now you know Isabelle Pharaoh, right?
Sekarang Anda tahu Isabelle Pharaoh, kan?
- No, that doesn't ring a bell. - Don't lie to me!
- Tidak, itu tidak mengingatkanku padamu. - Jangan berbohong padaku!
[Intense music]
[Musik yang intens]
Hey, Link, are you listening?
Hei, Link, apakah kamu mendengarkan?
Unfortunately.
Sayangnya.
Okay, run a background check on...
Oke, jalankan pemeriksaan latar belakang pada...
- What the hell was her name? - Isabel Faraón.
- Siapa sih namanya? - Isabel Faraón.
Isabel Faraón. Do the whole range.
Isabel Faraón. Lakukan semuanya.
I just don't understand. It has to be here.
Aku tidak mengerti. Itu harusnya ada di sini.
[sigh] Shawn, it's a decoy box.
[sigh] Shawn, itu kotak umpan.
[Intense music continues]
[Musik intens berlanjut]
[phone ringing]
[telepon berdering]
- We are the bank robbers. - [Amy] Hello, Link.
- Kami perampok bank. - [Amy] Halo, Link.
- Amy, is that you? - Mm-hmm.
- Amy, apakah itu kamu? - Mm-hmm.
[Link] Oh my god, it's been forever!
[Link] Ya ampun, sudah lama sekali!
Yes, I know, right? How are you?
Ya, saya tahu, kan? Apa kabar?
I've been fine. And you, still running?
Aku baik-baik saja. Dan kamu, masih berlari?
No, I took out my hip a couple of years ago.
Tidak, pinggulku cedera beberapa tahun lalu.
weeks doing field work.
minggu melakukan kerja lapangan.
Ugh, I hate when that happens.
Ugh, aku benci saat itu terjadi.
Ready for this one?
Siap untuk yang ini?
I'm sure.
Saya yakin.
It just doesn't look like Mason.
Itu tidak seperti Mason.
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
¿Shawn?
"Shawn?"
Can I talk to Mason?
Bisakah saya bicara dengan Mason?
[Link] Sure, no problem. Just a second.
[Link] Tentu, tidak masalah. Tunggu sebentar.
[phone rings]
[telepon berdering]
[Link exhala]
[Link hembuskan napas]
- Hey, boss? - [Mason] Yeah?
Hei, bos? [Mason] Ya?
I have the negotiator on the phone.
Saya sedang berbicara dengan negosiator di telepon.
Okay. I have to go.
Baiklah. Aku harus pergi.
If it moves, you shoot it.
Jika bergerak, tembak saja.
[sirens blaring]
[suara sirene meraung]
[footsteps knocking]
[suara langkah kaki yang mengetuk]
You should probably sit down for this.
Anda mungkin harus duduk untuk ini.
- Oh yeah? - [Link] Yes.
- Oh ya? - [Link] Ya.
[chair rattles]
[suara kursi bergetar]
- [phone rings] - Go ahead.
- [telepon berdering] - Silakan.
[Amy] Hola, Mason.
[Amy] Halo, Mason.
[bright music]
[musik yang cerah]
-¿Amy? - Network.
-¿Amy? - Jaringan.
How are you?
Apa kabarmu?
It does pretty well, you know, considering.
Itu berjalan cukup baik, lho, jika mempertimbangkannya.
[Bright music continues]
[Musik ceria terus berlanjut]
No, that's a lie.
Tidak, itu bohong.
It's, it's, you know, pretty tacky to be honest.
Ini, ini, Anda tahu, cukup norak sejujurnya.
But now that I hear your voice, no, it's not bad.
Tapi sekarang aku mendengar suaramu, tidak, itu tidak buruk.
- You sound great. - Thank you.
Kedengarannya hebat. - Terima kasih.
They.
Mereka.
..I've been busting my ass with this field work. Oh yeah? How's it going?
..Saya sudah bekerja keras di lapangan. Oh ya? Bagaimana kabarnya?
Well, I got promoted to the special unit.
Baiklah, saya dipromosikan ke unit khusus.
Really? Well, that's good.
Benarkah? Baiklah, itu bagus.
I'm happy for you. It couldn't have happened to a better person.
Saya turut berbahagia untuk Anda. Tidak ada orang lain yang lebih baik dari Anda yang mengalami hal ini.
So, I have to ask, is the FBI hosting this party?
Jadi, saya harus bertanya, apakah FBI yang menyelenggarakan pesta ini?
Yes, you are not wrong.
Ya, Anda tidak salah.
Of course they caught you. The cars came quickly, huh?
Tentu saja mereka menangkapmu. Mobil-mobil datang dengan cepat, ya?
You had an advantage.
Anda memiliki keuntungan.
[Amy] Yes, we noticed the chat
[Amy] Ya, kami memperhatikan obrolannya
of the whites a couple of weeks ago.
orang kulit putih beberapa minggu yang lalu.
Oh, of course, Shawn. Careless.
Oh, tentu saja, Shawn. Ceroboh.
[Amy] I'm sure that only
[Amy] Aku yakin itu saja
was trying to help you in his own way.
mencoba membantu Anda dengan caranya sendiri.
Hi Amy, it's me, I'm glad it's you.
Hai Amy, ini aku, aku senang itu kamu.
Uh, I couldn't help but notice that
Eh, aku tidak bisa tidak memperhatikannya
its internal surveillance is dark.
pengawasan internalnya gelap.
Link did an excellent job
Link telah melakukan pekerjaan yang sangat baik
controlling the seats in its perimeter.
mengendalikan kursi-kursi di sekelilingnya.
Well, she's the best, isn't she?
Ya, dia yang terbaik, bukan?
Um, I guess we should get to business.
Hmm, kurasa kita harus langsung ke intinya.
[Mason] Well, okay.
[Mason] Baiklah.
Okay, this is the part where
Oke, ini adalah bagian dimana
you say you have everything covered.
Anda mengatakan Anda telah mencakup segalanya.
The entrance, the exits, you have tactics, you have
Pintu masuk, pintu keluar, Anda punya taktik, Anda punya
snipers, you have electronic surveillance.
penembak jitu, Anda memiliki pengawasan elektronik.
And I in turn tell you that I have a
Dan saya pada gilirannya memberitahu Anda bahwa saya memiliki
bunch of hostages and I don't want to hurt them.
sekelompok sandera dan aku tidak ingin menyakiti mereka.
But, you know, if you come in, I have to
Tapi, kau tahu, jika kau masuk, aku harus
make blah, blah, blah, blah, blah to everyone
membuat semua orang berkata bla, bla, bla, bla, bla
and each of them, what's new?
dan masing-masingnya, apa yang baru?
How many hostages?
Berapa banyak sandera?
[Mason] Twenty-three, if you include staff and security.
[Mason] Dua puluh tiga, jika Anda termasuk staf dan keamanan.
Okay, well, if Anton is in charge of controlling
Oke baiklah kalau Anton yang bertugas mengontrol
crowds, I'm sure you are in good hands.
orang banyak, saya yakin Anda berada di tangan yang baik.
Well, then I have a special request.
Baiklah, kalau begitu saya punya permintaan khusus.
[Amy] Okay, shoot. I'll do my best.
[Amy] Oke, ayo. Aku akan berusaha sebaik mungkin.
I need 50 feet.
Saya butuh 50 kaki.
- 50 feet? - 50 feet.
- 50 kaki? - 50 kaki.
Why 50 feet?
Mengapa 50 kaki?
I mean, that's new.
Maksudku, itu baru.
Oh, I don't know, Amy.
Oh, aku tidak tahu, Amy.
I guess I feel a little claustrophobic.
Kurasa aku merasa sedikit klaustrofobia.
Sides, front of the building, all
Sisi, depan gedung, semuanya
back, police, tacticians, everyone.
kembali, polisi, ahli taktik, semuanya.
Oh, and it includes the sidewalk.
Oh, dan itu termasuk trotoar.
- [dramatic music] - [sirens blaring]
- [musik dramatis] - [suara sirene]
You know how I get when I'm cornered.
Kau tahu bagaimana perasaanku saat terpojok.
[Link] What do you think he's doing?
[Link] Menurut Anda apa yang sedang dia lakukan?
[laughs] He's trying to figure out 50 feet.
[tertawa] Dia mencoba menghitung jarak 50 kaki.
[Dramatic music continues]
[Musik dramatis berlanjut]
[Link] She doesn't look so comfortable in that outfit.
[Link] Dia tampak tidak nyaman dengan pakaian itu.
It's not her.
Itu bukan dia.
[Mason] No, it's not bad. I kinda like it.
[Mason] Tidak, tidak buruk. Aku agak menyukainya.
Oh, she looks good.
Oh, dia terlihat cantik.
Oh, she looks great.
Oh, dia tampak hebat.
And he's got that little boost of confidence in his voice.
Dan dia memiliki sedikit dorongan percaya diri dalam suaranya.
Like when he beats you at pool?
Seperti saat dia mengalahkanmu di kolam renang?
No, she never beat me at pool.
Tidak, dia tidak pernah mengalahkanku di kolam renang.
But [sighs] he's really doing well, isn't he?
Tapi [menghela napas] dia benar-benar melakukannya dengan baik, bukan?
[laughs] Wow.
[tertawa] Wow.
[Dramatic music continues]
[Musik dramatis berlanjut]
Captain, I'm going to need a 360 degree sweep of the perimeter.
Kapten, saya akan melakukan sapuan 360 derajat pada perimeter.
Okay, I'll let you negotiate, but
Oke, aku akan membiarkanmu bernegosiasi, tapi
I am still in charge of this operation.
Saya masih bertanggung jawab atas operasi ini.
And I'll let you keep that narrative
Dan aku akan membiarkanmu menyimpan narasi itu
as long as you do what I tell you.
Asalkan kamu melakukan apa yang aku perintahkan.
[garbled radio chatter]
[obrolan radio yang tidak jelas]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Sniper 3 in position. 52 feet.
Penembak jitu 3 di posisi. 52 kaki.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[clears throat] So nothing within 50 feet.
[berdeham] Jadi tidak ada apa pun dalam jarak 50 kaki.
Nothing at all.
Tidak ada sama sekali.
There has to be something or I wouldn't have ordered it.
Pasti ada sesuatu atau saya tidak akan memesannya.
Okay, there's a protocol we follow here,
Oke, ada protokol yang kami ikuti di sini,
trade-offs, escalation, sweat equity.
trade-off, eskalasi, ekuitas keringat.
We make an hour seem like 10.
Kita membuat satu jam terasa seperti 10.
Then when the sun goes down we drill hard.
Lalu ketika matahari terbenam, kami mengebor dengan keras.
I know the protocol and so does he.
Saya tahu protokolnya, dan dia pun tahu.
If you don't believe that Mason is one step
Jika Anda tidak percaya bahwa Mason adalah satu langkah
ahead of us, you are a fool.
di depan kita, kamu bodoh.
Mason is a wolf.
Mason adalah seekor serigala.
He will bite his own leg off to get out of a trap.
Dia akan menggigit kakinya sendiri untuk keluar dari perangkap.
Yeah, you and he are pretty close, aren't you?
Ya, kamu dan dia cukup dekat, bukan?
How do I know you're not helping him?
Bagaimana saya tahu Anda tidak membantunya?
Why should I trust you?
Mengapa saya harus percaya pada Anda?
It doesn't matter if you trust me.
Tidak masalah jika kau memercayaiku.
It is important that your superiors do so.
Penting bagi atasan Anda untuk melakukan hal itu.
Upload that, please.
Tolong unggah itu.
I have known exclusively the identity
Saya hanya mengetahui identitasnya
of one of the alleged thieves of
salah satu tersangka pencuri
banks, and it is none other than Mason Andrew Goddard.
bank, dan tidak lain adalah Mason Andrew Goddard.
My sources confirm that it is the notorious
Sumber saya mengonfirmasi bahwa itu adalah yang terkenal
international criminal, the ace of spades.
penjahat internasional, as sekop.
Okay, we have black iced coffee.
Oke, kami punya kopi hitam es.
Do you want some, uh, cream with that?
Kamu mau krim juga?
We have hazelnuts. We have vanilla.
Kami punya hazelnut. Kami punya vanili.
Ugh, gross. That's a joke, right?
Ih, menjijikkan. Itu cuma candaan, kan?
What's happening?
Apa yang terjadi?
The tactical team looks serious.
Tim taktis tampak serius.
- Oh yeah. - Aren't you worried?
Oh ya. - Kamu tidak khawatir?
No, that's what she wants us to be, worried.
Tidak, itu yang dia inginkan dari kita, khawatir.
so that we make a mistake and slip up.
sehingga kita melakukan kesalahan dan tergelincir.
Okay. If there is a decoy box, there is a hidden account I need you to find it.
Oke. Kalau ada kotak umpan, berarti ada akun tersembunyi. Aku ingin kamu menemukannya.
And what we should do is look for our escape route.
Dan yang seharusnya kita lakukan adalah mencari jalan keluar.
No
TIDAK
no no.
tidak, tidak.
That's what she wants, okay?
Itu yang dia inginkan, oke?
We just have to stay one step ahead of her.
Kita hanya harus tetap selangkah lebih maju darinya.
[radio crackling]
[suara radio berderak]
Yes, yes. Okay, I'll be there.
Ya, ya. Baiklah, aku akan ke sana.
Now listen, don't think too much about this.
Sekarang dengarkan, jangan terlalu banyak memikirkan hal ini.
Okay? I'll buy you all the time you need.
Oke? Aku akan membelikanmu kapan pun kamu butuh.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Oh!
Oh!
[Antón] That's it. All about me, all about me.
[Antón] Itu saja. Semua tentang saya, semua tentang saya.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
Look down. Stay to the right of that wall.
Lihat ke bawah. Tetaplah di sebelah kanan tembok itu.
[Hector] Let's pick up the pace, people!
[Hector] Ayo kita tingkatkan kecepatannya, teman-teman!
Come on. Let's move!
Ayo. Kita bergerak!
Let's go!
Ayo berangkat!
Face down. Don't look at me, man.
Menunduk. Jangan lihat aku, kawan.
[Hector] Keep your eyes forward!
[Hector] Tetap fokus ke depan!
[stomping footsteps]
[langkah kaki yang menghentak]
Yes, we have it clear here.
Ya, kami jelaskan di sini.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[Anton] Everybody make yourself comfortable.
[Anton] Buatlah dirimu nyaman.
We'll find out about some food and drink in a minute.
Kita akan tahu tentang beberapa makanan dan minuman sebentar lagi.
Get to know each other, relax.
Kenali satu sama lain, santai.
Consider this a vacation from your busy lives, friends.
Anggaplah ini sebagai liburan dari kesibukan hidup Anda, teman-teman.
- What do you need? - Food and drinks.
- Apa yang Anda butuhkan? - Makanan dan minuman.
Alright.
Baiklah.
Hector and I control this entire room.
Hector dan aku mengendalikan seluruh ruangan ini.
- Isn't that right, Hec? - Yes, sir!
- Benar kan, Hec? - Ya, Tuan!
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
Okay, just so you know, there is a plan.
Oke, sekadar informasi, ada rencana.
You are the boss.
Anda adalah bosnya.
[Suspense music continues]
[Musik menegangkan berlanjut]
[birds chirping]
[kicauan burung]
Are you sure we can't find something visual?
Apakah Anda yakin kami tidak dapat menemukan sesuatu yang visual?
Maybe just an old security camera in the hallway?
Mungkin hanya kamera keamanan lama di lorong?
I mean, anything.
Maksudku, apa saja.
She slammed it all shut.
Dia membanting semuanya hingga tertutup.
Landlines, feeds, everything. She is a professional.
Telepon rumah, feed, semuanya. Dia seorang profesional.
Yes I know.
Ya, aku tahu.
The Mossad subcontracted it.
Mossad mensubkontrakkannya.
Alright.
Baiklah.
There are 23 hostages.
Ada 23 sandera.
They were all smart devices.
Semuanya adalah perangkat pintar.
But you know, Anton didn't let them keep any of them.
Tapi tahukah Anda, Anton tidak mengizinkan mereka menyimpan satupun dari mereka.
But a technician with your skills will probably
Namun teknisi dengan keterampilan Anda mungkin akan
could turn it back on remotely.
dapat mengaktifkannya kembali dari jarak jauh.
Yeah?
Ya?
OK that's fine.
Baiklah, itu bagus.
I have something here. Just a second.
Saya punya sesuatu di sini. Tunggu sebentar.
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
Wait, is that spa music?
Tunggu, apakah itu musik spa?
Wow.
Wow.
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
Bright.
Terang.
[zipper scrapers]
[pengikis ritsleting]
[phone ringing]
[telepon berdering]
Command trailer.
Trailer perintah.
It's for you.
Ini untukmu.
[button beep]
[tombol berbunyi]
That spa music was a nice touch.
Musik spa itu adalah sentuhan yang bagus.
So you can remotely control someone's personal device.
Jadi Anda dapat mengendalikan perangkat pribadi seseorang dari jarak jauh.
Isn't that illegal, Amy?
Bukankah itu ilegal, Amy?
It's a grey area.
Itu wilayah abu-abu.
Mmm. I can't help but notice the buildup.
Hmm. Saya tidak bisa tidak memperhatikan penumpukannya.
[Amy] Yeah, the troops are getting restless.
[Amy] Ya, pasukan mulai gelisah.
Mmm. Yeah, well, we're worried here too.
Hmm. Ya, kami juga khawatir.
Well, I have a request for you.
Baiklah, aku punya permintaan untukmu.
It's not fair. I gave you 50
Ini tidak adil. Aku memberimu 50
feet, you have given me nothing.
kaki, kau tidak memberiku apa pun.
Nobody gets hurt, that's fair.
Tidak ada seorang pun yang terluka, itu adil.
What do you want?
Apa yang kamu inginkan?
I want two dozen pizzas. A mixed variety.
Saya mau dua lusin pizza. Berbagai macam.
And a Hawaiian for Shawn.
Dan orang Hawaii untuk Shawn.
And then for a few drinks, let's have a
Dan kemudian untuk minum-minum, mari kita minum.
soda mix, a little water, maybe
campuran soda, sedikit air, mungkin
an apple juice for the kid and beer for me.
jus apel untuk anak dan bir untukku.
In less than 30 minutes.
Dalam waktu kurang dari 30 menit.
- Anything else? - Yes.
- Ada lagi? - Ya.
I want you to hand it over. Alone.
Aku ingin kau menyerahkannya. Sendirian.
On the steps.
Di tangga.
The stopwatch started.
Stopwatch mulai bekerja.
And don't forget the beer.
Dan jangan lupa birnya.
Beer? Don't you think it's a little premature?
Bir? Tidakkah menurutmu itu agak terlalu dini?
Have some faith in me, will you?
Percayalah padaku, ya?
And I'll see you in less than 30 minutes.
Dan saya akan menemui Anda dalam waktu kurang dari 30 menit.
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
- [snapping fingers] - [upbeat music]
- [menjentikkan jari] - [musik yang ceria]
- Hi, Shawn. - [Shawn] Yeah?
Hai, Shawn./ [Shawn] Ya?
Check the lure box, will you?
Periksa kotak umpannya, ya?
Check all personal things,
Periksa semua barang pribadi,
like rings, lockets, whatever.
seperti cincin, liontin, apa pun.
Just give me the numbers you find.
Berikan saja saya angka yang Anda temukan.
Like any number.
Seperti angka apa pun.
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
[lid thuds]
[tutupnya bunyi]
[Shawn] You knew this was a decoy box, right?
[Shawn] Kau tahu ini kotak umpan, kan?
We have thousands of clients.
Kami memiliki ribuan klien.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Saya tidak mengerti apa yang Anda bicarakan.
[Shawn] Yeah, sure.
[Shawn] Ya, tentu.
I sense a little tension between you and your brother.
Saya merasakan sedikit ketegangan antara kamu dan saudaramu.
How do you know he's my brother?
Bagaimana kamu tahu dia saudaraku?
Hey, take a step back.
Hei, mundur selangkah.
- Come back. - Guess.
- Kembalilah. - Tebak.
You confirmed it.
Anda mengonfirmasinya.
You know, I have an older brother too.
Kau tahu, aku juga punya kakak laki-laki.
Bossy.
Suka memerintah.
I just hate Christmas gatherings because of that.
Saya benci acara kumpul-kumpul Natal karena itu.
Yes, no matter what he says or does, he
Ya, tidak peduli apa yang dia katakan atau lakukan, dia
There is always someone better than me.
Selalu ada seseorang yang lebih baik dariku.
Yeah, Mason is not like that.
Ya, Mason tidak seperti itu.
He treats you like a child.
Dia memperlakukanmu seperti anak kecil.
I mean, this was supposed to be your big result.
Maksudku, ini seharusnya menjadi hasil besarmu.
Now look, you're relegated to
Sekarang lihat, kamu diturunkan ke
holding the bank manager hostage.
menyandera manajer bank.
I screwed up, I deserve it.
Aku mengacau, aku pantas menerimanya.
Well, is that what it makes you think?
Nah, apakah itu yang membuat Anda berpikir?
Enough! You don't know what the hell
Cukup! Kamu tidak tahu apa-apa
you're talking, okay bro?
kamu ngomong ya, bro?
Take a step back.
Mundur selangkah.
Hello, Link?
Halo, Link?
[Link] Do you still have anything?
[Link] Apakah Anda masih punya sesuatu?
I think I found your number.
Saya pikir saya menemukan nomor Anda.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Around 24 hostages in
Sekitar 24 sandera di
this moment, and still
saat ini, dan masih
We are waiting for the
Kami sedang menunggu
initial hostages are released.
sandera awal dibebaskan.
[but at this time we don't know how long it will take]
[tapi saat ini kami tidak tahu berapa lama waktu yang dibutuhkan]
upbeat music. Oops.
musik yang ceria. Ups.
Here she comes. - [soft, cheerful music] - [birds chirping]
Ini dia datang. - [musik lembut dan ceria] - [kicauan burung]
[soft, cheerful music]
[musik lembut dan ceria]
- [Amy exhales sharply] - [soft, upbeat music]
- [Amy menghembuskan napas tajam] - [musik lembut dan ceria]
Hello.
Halo.
I'd invite you in, but uh, lots of people staring.
Aku ingin mengundangmu masuk, tapi banyak sekali orang yang menatap.
There is that, yes.
Ada itu, ya.
How many sights am I on right now?
Ada berapa tempat wisata yang saya kunjungi saat ini?
Uh, I would say around 12.
Eh, saya kira sekitar 12.
Mmmm, great turnout.
Mmmm, banyak sekali yang hadir.
- I know, right? - Yes.
- Aku tahu, kan? - Ya.
You are a popular boy.
Kamu seorang anak yang populer.
Hey, I'm sorry I turned you into the
Hei, maafkan aku karena telah mengubahmu menjadi
pizza delivery girl, but it's the only way.
gadis pengantar pizza, tapi itu satu-satunya cara.
I could do a face to face,
Aku bisa melakukannya secara langsung,
you know, just you and me and of course,
kamu tahu, hanya kamu dan aku dan tentu saja,
all the others, but...
semua yang lain, tapi...
So, I'm going to need two
Jadi, aku butuh dua
hostages, non-negotiable, give in order to receive.
sandera, tidak bisa dinegosiasikan, memberi agar menerima.
Well.
Dengan baik.
And after that, two every hour.
Dan setelah itu, dua setiap jam.
Okay, okay.
Oke, oke.
You're not even going to fight back?
Kau bahkan tidak akan melawan?
Why? It's a good and fair deal.
Mengapa? Ini adalah kesepakatan yang baik dan adil.
Are you exercising?
Apakah Anda berolahraga?
Uh, uh, I mean, a little bit.
Eh, eh, maksudku, sedikit.
They.
Mereka.
.. I think it's just legwork. You know what would be cool?
.. Menurutku itu hanya kerja keras. Kau tahu apa yang akan keren?
Yes, after all this is over,
Ya, setelah semua ini berakhir,
We went to our little private island and that's it.
Kami pergi ke pulau pribadi kecil kami dan hanya itu.
you know, the one with the fishing pier and the garden?
Anda tahu, yang ada dermaga pemancingan dan tamannya?
I just don't want anyone to get hurt.
Aku hanya tidak ingin siapapun terluka.
No, you don't have to worry about that.
Tidak, Anda tidak perlu khawatir tentang itu.
But this is not going to end well.
Tapi ini tidak akan berakhir dengan baik.
Well, maybe, maybe not.
Yah, mungkin, mungkin tidak.
Look, at some point, the gloves
Lihat, di suatu titik, sarung tangan
They will fall and people will get hurt.
Mereka akan jatuh dan orang-orang akan terluka.
Well, first of all, I didn't plan this.
Ya, pertama-tama saya tidak merencanakan ini.
This is Shawn, okay?
Ini Shawn, oke?
And I'm just here to bail him out.
Dan aku di sini hanya untuk menyelamatkannya.
After what happened with
Setelah apa yang terjadi dengan
we, I retired, just so you know.
kami, saya pensiun, sekadar agar Anda tahu.
So surrender now.
Jadi menyerahlah sekarang.
I can't do that. We'd all go to prison.
Aku tidak bisa melakukan itu. Kita semua akan masuk penjara.
Well, it's better than dying under a hail of bullets.
Ya, itu lebih baik daripada mati dihujani peluru.
I know about that.
Saya tahu tentang itu.
My dad died in prison.
Ayah saya meninggal di penjara.
I think I would have chosen the hailstorm.
Saya pikir saya akan memilih badai es.
I need my two hostages.
Aku butuh dua sanderaku.
And I need my pizza.
Dan aku butuh pizzaku.
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
- [shoes clinking] - [soft music]
- [suara sepatu berdenting] - [musik lembut]
Alright, pizza, pizza, man. Let's go.
Baiklah, pizza, pizza, kawan. Ayo.
Cold or hot, eat it.
Dingin atau panas, makanlah.
Just put it in your fucking stomach and shut up.
Masukkan saja ke perutmu dan diam saja.
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
- Honey, do you want to go home? - [woman] Please.
- Sayang, kamu mau pulang? - [wanita] Ayo.
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
- [shoes clinking] - [soft music]
- [suara sepatu berdenting] - [musik lembut]
[news chatter overlay]
[hamparan obrolan berita]
[Reporter] ...that two of the hostages have been released.
[Reporter] ...bahwa dua sandera telah dibebaskan.
[Reporter 2] Two hostages have been released.
[Reporter 2] Dua sandera telah dibebaskan.
- The negotiators are... - [news chatter overlay]
- Para negosiatornya adalah... - [hamparan obrolan berita]
Well, what do you have?
Baiklah, apa yang kamu punya?
So I put 2-1-3-4 on the
Jadi saya menempatkan 2-1-3-4 di
algorithm and you'll never believe it.
algoritma dan Anda tidak akan pernah mempercayainya.
[laughs] Oh, you have to agree.
[tertawa] Oh, Anda harus setuju.
Yes, to Isabelle Pharoah.
Ya, untuk Isabelle Pharoah.
Of course, it's dark standard security stuff
Tentu saja, ini adalah standar keamanan gelap
web, but you know, without the number, you won't find the name.
web, tetapi Anda tahu, tanpa nomor, Anda tidak akan menemukan nama tersebut.
- Yes, yes, this is good. - Yes.
- Ya, ya, ini bagus. - Ya.
Shawn, this is good.
Shawn, ini bagus.
Just look for box 2-1-3-4.
Cari saja kotak 2-1-3-4.
[Shawn] I'm telling you, there's no 2-1-3-4 here.
[Shawn] Aku bilang padamu, tidak ada 2-1-3-4 di sini.
All boxes start with one.
Semua kotak dimulai dengan angka satu.
Okay, you know what?
Oke, kamu tahu apa?
I... think it's time for me to have
Aku... pikir sudah waktunya bagiku untuk memiliki
a little chat with Mr. Manager.
mengobrol sebentar dengan Tuan Manajer.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ya, ya, ya, ya, ya, ya, ya.
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
[Gun shots]
[Suara tembakan]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [hand clapping] - [suspenseful music]
- [tepuk tangan] - [musik menegangkan]
[Link] Boss, we have a problem in the vault.
[Link] Bos, kami punya masalah di brankas.
- [upbeat music] - [shoes clinking]
- [musik yang ceria] - [suara sepatu berdenting]
¿Shawn?
"Shawn?"
What the fuck is going on?
Apa yang sebenarnya terjadi?
Where did he go?
Ke mana dia pergi?
He took off running.
Dia mulai berlari.
- Where's your gun? - He took it.
- Mana senjatamu? - Dia mengambilnya.
When have I ever shot anyone, Mason?
Kapan aku pernah menembak seseorang, Mason?
Well, I'm not talking about the head.
Baiklah, saya tidak berbicara tentang kepala.
Ah, get up.
Ah, bangun.
The leg or the arm or something like that.
Kaki atau lengan atau apalah sejenisnya.
- [upbeat music] - [shoes clinking]
- [musik yang ceria] - [suara sepatu berdenting]
[Mason] Link, notice.
[Mason] Link, perhatikan.
We need a total lockdown.
Kita perlu karantina wilayah total.
Reverse vault surveillance.
Pengawasan brankas terbalik.
I'm already on it.
Saya sudah mengerjakannya.
- [upbeat music] - [shoes clinking]
- [musik yang ceria] - [suara sepatu berdenting]
I lost it in the free elevator.
Saya kehilangannya di lift gratis.
He heads to the roof and is armed.
Dia menuju ke atap dan bersenjata.
Proceed with caution.
Lanjutkan dengan hati-hati.
- [suspenseful music] - [shoes clicking]
- [musik menegangkan] - [suara sepatu berbunyi klik]
- [door rattling] - [door slamming]
- [suara pintu berderak] - [suara pintu dibanting]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
You're going to throw this in my face, aren't you?
Kau akan melemparkan ini ke wajahku, bukan?
I'm not saying anything.
Saya tidak mengatakan apa-apa.
That's a yes.
Itu jawabannya ya.
[soft music]
[musik lembut]
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
[Upbeat music continues]
[Musik yang ceria terus berlanjut]
- [Mason] Link, lights on. - [upbeat music]
- [Mason] Link, lampu menyala. - [musik yang ceria]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [panting] - [suspenseful music]
- [terengah-engah] - [musik menegangkan]
-Shawn. - [upbeat music]
-Shawn. - [musik ceria]
[upbeat music]
[musik yang ceria]
Link, southeast door, close it.
Link, pintu tenggara, tutup.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [door knob rattles] - [suspenseful music]
- [gagang pintu bergetar] - [musik menegangkan]
Well, that was stimulating.
Wah, itu merangsang.
Drop the gun.
Jatuhkan senjatanya.
Drop the damn gun.
Jatuhkan senjatamu.
I'm not Shawn, are you sure?
Aku bukan Shawn, kau yakin?
[grunts]
[mendengus]
Alright.
Baiklah.
Take us to safe house 2-1-3-4.
Bawa kami ke rumah aman 2-1-3-4.
[breathing deeply] It's not a box.
[bernapas dalam-dalam] Itu bukan kotak.
Very few people know that the building
Sangat sedikit orang yang tahu bahwa gedung tersebut
next door is part of the bank.
di sebelahnya adalah bagian dari bank.
It's for our special accounts.
Ini untuk akun khusus kita.
Its location is a secret even
Lokasinya pun masih dirahasiakan
for the owners themselves
untuk pemiliknya sendiri
accounts, so they cannot be blackmailed.
akun, sehingga tidak dapat diperas.
Okay, so how do we get there?
Baiklah, jadi bagaimana kita sampai ke sana?
You walk on the sidewalk.
Anda berjalan di trotoar.
Well.
Dengan baik.
You'll find another way to get there.
Anda akan menemukan cara lain untuk sampai ke sana.
Please, I beg you.
Kumohon, aku mohon padamu.
Get out of this now while you still can.
Keluarlah dari sini sekarang selagi Anda masih bisa.
I... have a family.
Saya... punya keluarga.
We... don't want to hurt you.
Kami... tidak ingin menyakitimu.
All we want is this woman's crypto account.
Yang kami inginkan hanyalah akun kripto wanita ini.
That's all.
Itu saja.
You don't know who you're dealing with.
Anda tidak tahu dengan siapa Anda berhadapan.
When you find out what is
Ketika Anda mengetahui apa itu
passing by, will kill everyone in this
lewat, akan membunuh semua orang di sini
building to protect that account.
membangun untuk melindungi akun tersebut.
¿OMS?
Apaan?
Abel Salazar.
Abel Salazar.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Actually?
Sebenarnya?
The... the Abel Salazar?
Yang... Abel Salazar?
The billionaire who financed all
Miliarder yang membiayai semuanya
those coups and overthrew three governments?
kudeta tersebut dan menggulingkan tiga pemerintahan?
Yeah.
Ya.
And his lover is Isabelle Pharoah.
Dan kekasihnya adalah Isabelle Pharoah.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- We're dead. - [Shawn] I'm not following you.
- Kita mati. - [Shawn] Aku tidak mengikutimu.
It is a box of earth.
Itu adalah kotak berisi tanah.
It's... it's... it's that the most powerful people in the
Itu... itu... itu adalah orang-orang paling berkuasa di
world has its dirty little secrets in there.
Dunia ini punya rahasia-rahasia kecil yang kotor di sana.
And I tell you that it is the
Dan aku katakan padamu bahwa itu adalah
most serious lever imaginable.
tuas paling serius yang dapat dibayangkan.
How do you know there's real dirt in there?
Bagaimana Anda tahu ada kotoran sungguhan di sana?
Because nobody bothers to get to this level
Karena tidak ada seorang pun yang mau repot-repot mencapai level ini
to hide things unless everything is fucked up.
menyembunyikan sesuatu kecuali semuanya kacau.
And that-that decoy with the lover,
Dan itu-itu umpan dengan kekasih,
I don't know why the hell they trusted this to
Aku tidak tahu kenapa mereka mempercayai hal ini
this guy, for God's sake. And look at this.
orang ini, demi Tuhan. Dan lihat ini.
Our fan base is big, but not that big.
Basis penggemar kami besar, tetapi tidak sebesar itu.
Oh man. If I'm wrong, we're dead.
Ya ampun. Kalau aku salah, kita mati saja.
And if I'm right, we make the decisions.
Dan jika saya benar, kami yang membuat keputusan.
And we get the cryptography.
Dan kita mendapatkan kriptografinya.
[Link] We will need the schematics.
[Link] Kita akan membutuhkan skemanya.
Schematics? You have the schematics.
Skema? Anda punya skemanya.
You do.
Kau melakukannya.
[faces] Yes, in our system we do.
[wajah] Ya, dalam sistem kami begitu.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[police chattering]
[polisi berceloteh]
- [car engine revving] - [suspenseful music]
- [mesin mobil menderu] - [musik menegangkan]
- [door slamming] - [suspenseful music]
- [banting pintu] - [musik menegangkan]
[people talking indiscriminately]
[orang-orang berbicara tanpa pandang bulu]
- [door slamming] - [shoes clanking]
- [banting pintu] - [suara sepatu berdenting]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [Mr. Flores] Agent Decker. - Who's asking?
- [Tuan Flores] Agen Decker. - Siapa yang bertanya?
I'd like to talk to you.
Saya ingin berbicara dengan Anda.
So speak up.
Jadi, bicaralah.
Alone, please.
Sendirian, silakan.
I'll be right back.
Saya akan segera kembali.
Remember me again. Are you?
Ingat aku lagi. Kamu?
Mr. Flores.
Tuan Flores.
My client has an interest
Klien saya memiliki minat
staff at this establishment
staf di tempat ini
in particular and well, he is worried.
khususnya dan yah, dia khawatir.
Who is your client?
Siapa klien Anda?
Your superior knows who he is.
Atasan Anda tahu siapa dia.
Well, no need to worry.
Baiklah, tidak perlu khawatir.
I have everything under control.
Saya mengendalikan segalanya.
Is there a reason you haven't entered the building yet?
Apakah ada alasan Anda belum memasuki gedung tersebut?
Yes, they have been returning hostages as planned.
Ya, mereka telah memulangkan sandera sesuai rencana.
No one has been hurt. I have no reason to do so.
Tidak ada yang terluka. Saya tidak punya alasan untuk melakukannya.
My client's only concern is the safety of his property.
Satu-satunya perhatian klien saya adalah keamanan propertinya.
No one will leave that building
Tidak ada seorang pun yang akan meninggalkan gedung itu
with the property of your client.
dengan properti klien Anda.
You may not understand the gist of this, Agent Decker.
Anda mungkin tidak mengerti inti masalahnya, Agen Decker.
Secure this establishment
Amankan tempat ini
now or there will be an avalanche.
sekarang atau akan terjadi longsor.
And as you know, avalanches are all about gravity.
Dan seperti yang Anda ketahui, longsoran salju terjadi karena gravitasi.
Either you get out of the way or you'll be buried alive.
Entah kau minggir atau kau akan dikubur hidup-hidup.
Why don't you call Agent Richter if you have to?
Mengapa Anda tidak menelepon Agen Richter jika harus?
Ask him to give you a little more context.
Minta dia untuk memberi Anda sedikit lebih banyak konteks.
But please, for your own good, don't take too long.
Namun, demi kebaikan Anda sendiri, jangan memakan waktu terlalu lama.
- [shoes clicking] - [suspenseful music]
- [suara sepatu berbunyi klik] - [musik menegangkan]
- Let's go. - [suspense music]
- Ayo berangkat. - [musik menegangkan]
Link, speak up. Where, where are we going?
Link, bicaralah. Ke mana, ke mana kita akan pergi?
- Straight ahead. - Keep going, keep going.
- Lurus ke depan. - Terus maju, terus maju.
- So what? - [Link] Second pole, turn left.
- Jadi bagaimana? - [Link] Tiang kedua, belok kiri.
Second pole, turn left. Go ahead.
Tiang kedua, belok kiri. Silakan.
[Link] Okay.
[Link] Oke.
On the back wall, which is the end of the neighboring building,
Di dinding belakang, yang merupakan ujung bangunan tetangga,
X marks the spot.
X menandai titik tersebut.
- Is this it? - Yes.
- Benarkah ini? - Ya.
- Link? - Yes.
- Tautan? - Ya.
Okay, it's plastic. What do you have?
Oke, ini plastik. Apa yang kamu punya?
- It's drywall. I've got my mallet. - Good.
- Ini dinding. Aku punya palu. - Bagus.
Look, I bet you're glad I brought my gear now, huh?
Lihat, aku yakin kau senang aku membawa perlengkapanku sekarang, ya?
I'm very, very proud of you now. Now let's go.
Aku sangat, sangat bangga padamu sekarang. Sekarang mari kita mulai.
- Okay, back off. - Okay.
- Oke, mundur. - Oke.
I won't let you down, I promise.
Aku tidak akan mengecewakanmu, aku janji.
[Mason] I know, I know. Do it.
[Mason] Aku tahu, aku tahu. Lakukan saja.
[hammer blows]
[pukulan palu]
Come in. Go ahead.
Silakan masuk. Silakan.
- [bag bangs] - You're next.
- [menggedor tas] - Kamu selanjutnya.
- Let's go. - Yeah, I'm coming. [grunts]
- Ayo berangkat. - Ya, aku ikut. [menggerutu]
Shit.
Kotoran.
It's a fucking brick wall.
Itu tembok bata sialan.
Link, what do we do with this?
Link, apa yang kita lakukan dengan ini?
[Anton] Hey boss, it's time for the hostages.
[Anton] Hei bos, waktunya untuk para sandera.
Shawn, take out your gun.
Shawn, keluarkan senjatamu.
You get in the corner. Right now.
Sekarang, kamu berdiri di pojok.
Now listen, it moves, you shoot it, dammit.
Sekarang dengarkan, ia bergerak, kau tembak saja, sial.
- Okay? - Yeah, okay.
Oke? - Ya, oke.
I'm not kidding. I'll be right back.
Aku tidak bercanda. Aku akan segera kembali.
Hostages leaving!
Para sandera pergi!
Go ahead. Go.
Silakan. Lanjutkan.
And.
Dan.
[door knocking]
[mengetuk pintu]
Anton
Anton
- Yes, boss. - I need two more.
- Baik, Bos. - Saya butuh dua lagi.
Who are the medicators?
Siapakah para dokternya?
You, come. Now.
Kamu, kemarilah. Sekarang.
Let's go, let's go.
Ayo, ayo.
- Hey, get up, get up, get up. - Come on.
- Hei, bangun, bangun, bangun. - Ayo.
Quick quick.
Cepat cepat.
Okay, who's next on the list?
Oke, siapa berikutnya dalam daftar?
Two university students with their final exams.
Dua mahasiswa dengan ujian akhir mereka.
[Mason] All right, bring it. Bring it, bring it.
[Mason] Baiklah, bawa. Bawa, bawa.
- Cojelos. - Come on. Come on.
- Cojelos. - Ayo. Ayo.
Faster, move.
Lebih cepat, bergerak.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- Two more coming out! - [Officer] Hold fire.
- Dua lagi keluar! - [Petugas] Tahan tembakan.
Two more come out.
Dua lagi keluar.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
This way. Come on, come on.
Ke sini. Ayo, ayo.
DRD in position. Take them to the doctor.
DRD sudah siap. Bawa mereka ke dokter.
Eyes on the engine. Passing.
Perhatikan mesinnya. Melewati.
-[hammer bangs]-[Shawn growls]
-[pukulan palu]-[Shawn menggeram]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Well.
Dengan baik.
[Shawn panting]
[Shawn terengah-engah]
- [hammer banging] - [cement crashing]
- [memukul palu] - [menabrak semen]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [Mason] Let's go. - Okay, I'm going, I'm going.
- [Mason] Ayo berangkat. - Baiklah, aku berangkat, aku berangkat.
[men gasping]
[pria terengah-engah]
Ah.
Ah.
Court.
Pengadilan.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Look, you have to tell me something.
Dengar, kau harus memberitahuku sesuatu.
Who else have you ever talked to about this?
Dengan siapa lagi Anda pernah berbicara tentang hal ini?
Who told you about this job?
Siapa yang memberitahumu tentang pekerjaan ini?
Remember my friend Al from Los Angeles?
Ingat temanku Al dari Los Angeles?
He's a good guy. You've met him before.
Dia orang baik. Anda pernah bertemu dengannya sebelumnya.
Yeah, Al is the one who was in San Quentin 10 years ago, right?
Ya, Al adalah orang yang berada di San Quentin 10 tahun lalu, kan?
Yeah, hey, it must have gone out.
Ya, hei, pasti sudah padam.
Why are you questioning me about this?
Mengapa Anda menanyai saya tentang hal ini?
[Mason] Oh, God, I have to make a call, keep digging.
[Mason] Ya Tuhan, saya harus menelepon, terus menggali.
- [college girl] Hey, are you Decker? - Yeah.
- [mahasiswa] Hei, kamu Decker? - Ya.
Um, he asked me to give this to you.
Hmm, dia memintaku untuk memberikan ini padamu.
He.
Dia.
.
.
He said it was plan B.
Dia mengatakan itu rencana B.
Thanks. - [cell phone ringing] - Hey. Amy, I knew you were ruthless. But not this ruthless. What are you talking about?
Terima kasih. - [ponsel berdering] - Hei. Amy, aku tahu kau kejam. Tapi tidak sekejam ini. Apa yang kau bicarakan?
You used Al to get to my brother.
Kau menggunakan Al untuk menemui saudaraku.
Alabama?
Alabama?
Yes, you got him out of prison early.
Ya, Anda membebaskannya dari penjara lebih awal.
Then he convinced my brother for this job.
Lalu dia meyakinkan saudaraku untuk pekerjaan ini.
[Amy] That's not what's happening.
[Amy] Bukan itu yang terjadi.
So why this box? Amy, this box.
Jadi, mengapa kotak ini? Amy, kotak ini.
Do you want us all to be killed?
Apakah Anda ingin kita semua terbunuh?
No, of course not.
Tidak, tentu saja tidak.
Mason, I've been honest with you all this time.
Mason, aku sudah jujur ​​padamu selama ini.
Oh really, how about Miami?
Oh benarkah, bagaimana dengan Miami?
Was that real?
Apakah itu nyata?
Yeah, I mean, most of it.
Ya, maksudku, sebagian besarnya.
Obviously it's not the work part, but the rest is.
Jelas itu bukan bagian pekerjaannya, tapi sisanya.
[Mason] What about now?
[Mason] Bagaimana sekarang?
[sigh] Mason, I swear,
[desahan] Mason, aku bersumpah,
I don't know anything about this box.
Saya tidak tahu apa pun tentang kotak ini.
[Mason] Oh, don't you know, that this
[Mason] Oh, tidakkah kamu tahu, bahwa ini
was it the box of Salazar's lover?
apakah itu kotak kekasih Salazar?
You didn't know?
Anda tidak tahu?
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
¿Abel Salazar?
Apakah Abel Salazar?
Yeah, yeah, you headed him straight to his litter box.
Ya, ya, kamu mengarahkannya langsung ke kotak kotorannya.
[Amy] Okay, I'll have to call you back.
[Amy] Baiklah, aku akan meneleponmu kembali.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Oh, fuck.
Oh, sial.
-[phone ringing] -Decker.
-[telepon berdering] -Decker.
You set them up and used me to do it.
Anda menjebak mereka dan memanfaatkan saya untuk melakukannya.
If I had told you everything,
Jika aku sudah menceritakan semuanya padamu,
would you have continued?
apakah kamu akan melanjutkannya?
No, no, of course not.
Tidak, tidak, tentu saja tidak.
Exactly, I've already made my point clear.
Tepat sekali, saya sudah menjelaskan maksud saya.
What's in the box?
Apa isi kotaknya?
Wait.
Tunggu.
[people chatting]
[orang-orang mengobrol]
I am not at liberty to disclose that.
Saya tidak bebas mengungkapkannya.
information at this time, but what you
informasi saat ini, tetapi apa yang Anda
I can say that it is much bigger than you imagine.
Saya dapat katakan bahwa itu jauh lebih besar daripada yang Anda bayangkan.
Well, if this is so big,
Baiklah, jika ini sebesar ini,
why don't we confiscate it?
mengapa kita tidak menyitanya?
[Decker] Salazar's lawyers are the best.
[Decker] Pengacara Salazar adalah yang terbaik.
As soon as they had discovered that
Begitu mereka menemukan bahwa
We knew they would have blocked all the channels.
Kami tahu mereka akan memblokir semua saluran.
legal and the box would have magically disappeared.
sah dan kotak itu akan hilang secara ajaib.
Vern, I was contacted by Salazar's liaison, Mr. Flowers.
Vern, saya dihubungi oleh penghubung Salazar, Tuan Flowers.
They're not joking. They want to kill you all.
Mereka tidak bercanda. Mereka ingin membunuh kalian semua.
[Decker] Let's hope it doesn't come to that.
[Decker] Semoga saja hal itu tidak terjadi.
But can you shorten his leash a little?
Tetapi bisakah kamu memperpendek tali pengikatnya sedikit?
Give me some time!
Beri aku waktu!
Unfortunately, that time has passed.
Sayangnya, waktu itu telah berlalu.
Mr. Salazar has already slipped my mind.
Tuan Salazar telah hilang dari pikiranku.
How can this be?
Bagaimana ini bisa terjadi?
The fucking corrupt CIA.
CIA yang korup sekali.
They have activated joint special operations.
Mereka telah mengaktifkan operasi khusus gabungan.
By nightfall this will be under military jurisdiction.
Menjelang malam, wilayah ini akan berada di bawah yurisdiksi militer.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [Amy growls] - [phone bangs]
- [Amy menggeram] - [ponsel berbunyi]
- [helicopters buzzing] - [suspenseful music]
- [suara helikopter] - [musik menegangkan]
Link, where are we going?
Link, kita mau ke mana?
[Link] Straight ahead, follow the corridor for 20 meters.
[Link] Lurus ke depan, ikuti koridor sejauh 20 meter.
[Mason] Go straight.
[Mason] Jalan lurus saja.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[Officer] Now we check the way here, Sergeant!
[Petugas] Sekarang kita periksa jalan ke sini, Sersan!
[garbled radio chatter]
[obrolan radio yang tidak jelas]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[Mason] Correct.
[Mason] Benar.
[Mason] Okay, sure, sure.
[Mason] Oke, tentu, tentu.
Let's go, let's go.
Ayo, ayo.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[Shawn] This is the wall. Here.
[Shawn] Ini temboknya. Di sini.
[garbled radio chatter]
[obrolan radio yang tidak jelas]
- [hammer banging] - [cement crashing]
- [memukul palu] - [menabrak semen]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
That's how it is.
Begitulah adanya.
- [hammer banging] - [cement crashing]
- [memukul palu] - [menabrak semen]
All right, go ahead. Go ahead.
Baiklah, silakan. Silakan.
[drill whirring]
[bor berdengung]
What do we have?
Apa yang kita punya?
It is a steel plate in the middle.
Ada pelat baja di tengahnya.
It will take some time to drill.
Akan butuh waktu untuk mengebornya.
Can we use a C4?
Bisakah kita menggunakan C4?
No, no, that's too much attention.
Tidak, tidak, itu terlalu banyak perhatian.
Do you have the cobalt drill?
Apakah Anda memiliki bor kobalt?
- Yes. - Use that.
- Ya. - Gunakan itu.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [siren blaring] - [suspenseful music]
- [suara sirene] - [musik menegangkan]
- [garbled radio chatter] - [suspenseful music]
- [obrolan radio yang tidak jelas] - [musik yang menegangkan]
[phone ringing]
[telepon berdering]
What do you have?
Apa yang kamu punya?
They're taking over, JSOC.
Mereka mengambil alih, JSOC.
I can try to stop them, but
Aku bisa mencoba menghentikan mereka, tapi
Salazar ignored everyone.
Salazar mengabaikan semua orang.
Special ops, huh?
Operasi khusus, ya?
[Amy] Yes, but it's not worth losing your life over.
[Amy] Ya, tapi itu tidak sepadan dengan kehilangan nyawamu.
I mean, give yourself up while
Maksudku, serahkan dirimu saat
I still have the power to protect you.
Aku masih memiliki kekuatan untuk melindungimu.
Let me be your plan B, be smart.
Biarkan aku menjadi rencana B-mu, jadilah cerdas.
When have I ever been smart?
Kapankah saya pernah pintar?
Just let me know how I can help you.
Beri tahu saya saja bagaimana saya dapat membantu Anda.
You can reach out to all your media friends, make them sweat.
Anda dapat menjangkau semua teman media Anda, membuat mereka berkeringat.
I can try. I mean, it will take some time.
Aku bisa mencobanya. Maksudku, itu akan memakan waktu.
I... can't make any promises.
Saya... tidak bisa berjanji apa pun.
Oh, I believe in you.
Oh, aku percaya padamu.
- [garbled chatter] - [suspenseful music]
- [obrolan tak jelas] - [musik menegangkan]
[Keyboard keys clicking]
[Klik tombol keyboard]
¿Mason?
Tukang batu?
Commander Cyrus, JSOC.
Komandan Cyrus, JSOC.
Commander Cyrus, they are still releasing hostages.
Komandan Cyrus, mereka masih membebaskan sandera.
This has been a peaceful transaction.
Ini merupakan transaksi yang damai.
The FBI has surrendered its authority and is
FBI telah menyerahkan kewenangannya dan
operation is now under my jurisdiction.
operasinya sekarang berada di bawah yurisdiksi saya.
Rest assured, I should have this finished within an hour.
Tenang saja, saya akan menyelesaikannya dalam waktu satu jam.
Connect me to the bank's main line.
Hubungkan saya ke saluran utama bank.
[JSOC Operator] You got it, sir.
[Operator JSOC] Anda mengerti, Tuan.
You're welcome to stay, but just get out of our way.
Silakan tinggal, tapi minggir saja dari hadapan kami.
[Keyboard keys clicking]
[Klik tombol keyboard]
And.
Dan.
Whoever you are, you're too close.
Siapapun Anda, Anda terlalu dekat.
My name is Ciro, Special Operations Commander.
Nama saya Ciro, Komandan Operasi Khusus.
Conciliation is no longer an option and the
Konsiliasi bukan lagi sebuah pilihan dan
Negotiations have ended. Am I making myself clear?
Negosiasi telah berakhir. Apakah saya sudah menjelaskannya dengan jelas?
Special Ops, wow, we really hit a nerve here, didn't we?
Pasukan Khusus, wah, kita benar-benar menyentuh titik sensitif di sini, bukan?
You are going to free the remaining hostages.
Anda akan membebaskan sandera yang tersisa.
They will leave the bank in a single file.
Mereka akan meninggalkan bank dalam satu barisan.
And every time I give the signal,
Dan setiap kali aku memberi sinyal,
You and your crew will follow me.
Anda dan kru Anda akan mengikuti saya.
hands in the air. Hands in the air?
tangan di udara. Tangan di udara?
Well, how are we supposed to put our hands in the air?
Baiklah, bagaimana caranya kita mengacungkan tangan kita ke udara?
and- and push a- A wheelbarrow?
dan- dan dorong se- Sebuah gerobak dorong?
Forklift truck?
Truk forklift?
[Mason] Yeah, a wheelbarrow full of all the-
[Mason] Ya, gerobak dorong penuh dengan semua-
the land we found.
tanah yang kami temukan.
That's why you're here, isn't it?
Itulah mengapa Anda ada di sini, bukan?
because Salazar pulled some strings?
karena Salazar mengerahkan segala upaya?
Leave everything in the bank
Tinggalkan semuanya di bank
exactly where you found it.
tepat di tempat Anda menemukannya.
Exactly 15 minutes from the second in which
Tepat 15 menit dari detik dimana
end this call, we arrived with extreme prejudice.
mengakhiri panggilan ini, kami tiba dengan prasangka yang ekstrem.
Okay, I'm not the smartest guy in the world,
Oke, aku bukan orang terpintar di dunia,
but I know a threat when I hear one.
tetapi saya tahu adanya ancaman ketika saya mendengarnya.
So this is my answer to you.
Jadi ini jawabanku untukmu.
Okay, do you have a pen?
Oke, apakah kamu punya pena?
Okay, well, son, are you listening?
Baiklah, Nak, apakah kau mendengarkan?
Okay, okay, first word, fuck.
Oke, oke, kata pertama, sial.
Second word, you.
Kata kedua, kamu.
You will regret it.
Kamu akan menyesalinya.
Not as much as Salazar. Check your six o'clock.
Tidak sebanyak Salazar. Periksa jam enam Anda.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Well, there you have it, folks.
Baiklah, begitulah, teman-teman.
This is Jennifer Tish with Channel 13 News, stay tuned.
Ini Jennifer Tish dari Channel 13 News, nantikan terus.
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
Hi people, We are live in the center.
Hai semuanya, Kami siaran langsung di pusat.
There has been an escalation of police presence.
Telah terjadi peningkatan kehadiran polisi.
Tensions are rising.
Ketegangan meningkat.
[Mason] Woof, woof, boy, old man Sal's not gonna like that.
[Mason] Woof, woof, nak, si tua Sal tidak akan menyukainya.
[laughs] I hope you brought enough popcorn for all of us.
[tertawa] Saya harap Anda membawa cukup popcorn untuk kita semua.
The timer starts now.
Pengatur waktu mulai sekarang.
Well.
Dengan baik.
- [garbled chatter] - [suspenseful music]
- [obrolan tak jelas] - [musik menegangkan]
[cement breaking]
[pecahnya semen]
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Look at this one.
Lihat yang ini.
Wow [laughs], incredible.
Wow [tertawa], luar biasa.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Wow.
Wow.
Link, we need you here right now.
Link, kami membutuhkan Anda di sini sekarang.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Very proud of you.
Sangat bangga padamu.
- [laughs] Yeah, sure. - I really am.
- [tertawa] Ya, tentu saja. - Sungguh.
Let's go.
Ayo pergi.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
One more thing before you go.
Satu hal lagi sebelum Anda pergi.
Seriously, you guys have been the best,
Serius deh, kalian semua memang yang terbaik,
I mean, the best hostages with
Maksudku, sandera terbaik dengan
those I have had the pleasure of working with.
mereka yang pernah beruntung bisa bekerja bersama saya.
It has been an honor.
Merupakan suatu kehormatan.
I would like to say thank you.
Saya ingin mengucapkan terima kasih.
Anything you want to add, Hec?
Ada yang ingin ditambahkan, Hec?
Nope, you covered it, buddy.
Tidak, kamu sudah mengatasinya, sobat.
Saquémoslos.
Saquemoslos.
Come on, come on!
Ayo ayo!
Two at a time!
Dua sekaligus!
Clean it up! Hostages are coming out!
Bersihkan! Para sandera akan keluar!
[Anton] We have more to come out.
[Anton] Masih banyak lagi yang akan kami sampaikan.
Come on, come on, come on!
Ayo ayo ayo!
Keep moving!
Jalan terus!
Let's go!
Ayo berangkat!
Two more come out.
Dua lagi keluar.
Come on, get your ass out
Ayo, keluarkan pantatmu
you little son of a bitch!
dasar bajingan kecil!
Come on, Jheri Curl, you motherfucker!
Ayolah, Jheri Curl, kau bajingan!
Two more will come out!
Dua lagi akan keluar!
Move, move!
Bergerak, bergerak!
The last two rent-a-cops, Last two rent-a-cops!
Dua polisi sewaan terakhir, Dua polisi sewaan terakhir!
Come on, come on!
Ayo ayo!
Hey girl, there you have it.
Hai gadis, itu dia.
- There you go. - Ceasefire!
- Itu dia. - Gencatan senjata!
- [Caras mumbles] - [suspense music]
- [Caras bergumam] - [musik menegangkan]
81.
Nomor 81.
Ah, 81, 81, 81, 81, 81.
Ah, 81, 81, 81, 81, 81.
There it is.
Itu ada.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
It's a hard drive.
Itu adalah harddisk.
That's all?
Itu saja?
This is Mr. Salazar's personal impulse, correct.
Ini adalah dorongan pribadi Tn. Salazar, benar.
Is the crypto wallet there?
Apakah dompet kripto ada?
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
No, Shawn, this is a server farm.
Tidak, Shawn, ini adalah peternakan server.
private, a private cloud for the elite.
pribadi, cloud pribadi untuk kaum elit.
Okay, we need to get this up immediately.
Oke, kita harus menyelesaikan ini segera.
- How long will it take? - Mmm, 10 minutes.
- Butuh berapa lama? - Mmm, 10 menit.
We don't have 10 minutes. Come on, let's do this.
Kita tidak punya waktu 10 menit. Ayo, kita lakukan ini.
I'm on it.
Aku akan mengerjakannya.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
My family's life is now in your hands.
Hidup keluargaku sekarang ada di tanganmu.
-[suspenseful music]-[laptop beeps]
-[musik menegangkan]-[laptop berbunyi]
[phone ringing]
[telepon berdering]
- [Mason] Hey. - Hey.
- [Mason] Hei. - Hei.
Hey, listen, um, I got one last request.
Hei, dengar, um, aku punya satu permintaan terakhir.
[Amy] I'm listening.
[Amy] Aku mendengarkan.
When this is all over, Take care of my crew.
Ketika ini semua berakhir, Jagalah kru-ku.
Make sure they are in FBI custody.
Pastikan mereka berada dalam tahanan FBI.
Sorry, no..
Maaf, tidak..
.
.
I can't.
Saya tidak bisa.
I can't do that.
Saya tidak bisa melakukan itu.
[sighs] They've bypassed my authority. Come on, you're smarter than me. You'll think of something. You said... "my crew."
[menghela napas] Mereka telah melewati wewenangku. Ayolah, kau lebih pintar dariku. Kau akan memikirkan sesuatu. Kau bilang... "kruku."
. What about you?
. Bagaimana denganmu?
I will wait for you and see you on the island, I will share
Aku akan menunggumu dan melihatmu di pulau itu, aku akan berbagi
a bucket of beer, talking about nothing. [laughs]
seember bir, ngomong apa-apa. [tertawa]
Yes, I would really like that.
Ya, saya sungguh menginginkannya.
I need the name of that-
Aku butuh nama itu-
that man who approached you from Salazar.
pria yang mendekati Anda dari Salazar.
What was his name?
Siapa namanya?
Mr. Flores.
Tuan Flores.
Oh, that's a nice name.
Oh, itu nama yang bagus.
That's what he gave me.
Itulah yang dia berikan padaku.
Okay, Amy, take care of my crew and take care of yourself.
Baiklah, Amy, jaga kru-ku dan jaga dirimu sendiri.
[indistinct chatter]
[obrolan tidak jelas]
[siren sounds]
[suara sirene]
[sighs]
[menghela napas]
- [footsteps pounding] - [suspenseful music]
- [suara langkah kaki yang berirama] - [musik yang menegangkan]
- [engine humming] - [suspenseful music]
- [suara mesin berdengung] - [musik menegangkan]
Waiting, all clear.
Menunggu, semuanya aman.
[resuming operations]
[melanjutkan operasi]
suspenseful music. That's it, you're the last one. Mr. Caras, are you ready?
musik yang menegangkan. Itu saja, Anda yang terakhir. Tuan Caras, apakah Anda siap?
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Hostages leaving, last one!
Para sandera pergi, yang terakhir!
Let's go.
Ayo pergi.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
- [garbled chatter] - [suspenseful music]
- [obrolan tak jelas] - [musik menegangkan]
[Special Ops Officer] Ceasefire! Hostages leaving!
[Petugas Operasi Khusus] Gencatan senjata! Para sandera pergi!
He's coming out, move, move!
Dia keluar, bergerak, bergerak!
- [garbled chatter] - [suspenseful music]
- [obrolan tak jelas] - [musik menegangkan]
-[keyboard keys clicking]-[suspenseful music]
-[klik tombol keyboard]-[musik menegangkan]
About five minutes.
Sekitar lima menit.
[Mason] Just give me a minute.
[Mason] Beri aku waktu sebentar.
Okay, we'll do this one at a time.
Baiklah, kita akan bahas satu per satu.
You already know the dance with your hands in the air.
Anda sudah mengetahui tarian dengan tangan di udara.
Don't make any sudden movements. And put the
Jangan membuat gerakan tiba-tiba. Dan letakkan
cameras, because I need all the time I can get.
kamera, karena saya membutuhkannya sebanyak mungkin waktu.
stretch it
regangkan itu
Okay, who wants to be first?
Oke, siapa yang ingin menjadi yang pertama?
I will go.
Aku akan pergi.
Well.
Dengan baik.
Okay, bro.
Oke, saudara.
Stay safe out there, Hec.
Tetaplah aman di luar sana, Hec.
You are real.
Kamu nyata.
I'll be fine.
Aku akan baik-baik saja.
All right, guys.
Baiklah, teman-teman.
[footsteps knocking]
[suara langkah kaki yang mengetuk]
- [garbled radio chatter] - Coming out!
- [obrolan radio yang tidak jelas] - Keluar!
[Special Ops Officer] Both hands, both hands!
[Petugas Operasi Khusus] Kedua tangan, kedua tangan!
Let me see your hands, both of them!
Biarkan aku melihat tanganmu, keduanya!
Turn around and look at the building!
Berbaliklah dan lihatlah bangunan itu!
Look at the building!
Lihatlah bangunan itu!
Start walking backwards to the sound of my voice!
Mulailah berjalan mundur mengikuti suaraku!
Keep them coming!
Teruslah kirimkan!
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Get on your knees now!
Berlututlah sekarang!
- [garbled radio chatter] - [suspenseful music]
- [obrolan radio yang tidak jelas] - [musik yang menegangkan]
I guess I'm next.
Aku rasa aku berikutnya.
Shawn.
Shawn, siapa yang tidak kenal Shawn?
That's all.
Itu saja.
It's been an amazing ride, boss.
Benar-benar perjalanan yang menakjubkan, bos.
Proud to be in this gang.
Bangga berada di geng ini.
Take care of yourself, Anton.
Jaga dirimu baik-baik, Anton.
[Anton] You know it.
[Anton] Kau tahu itu.
[exhales deeply] Damn.
[menghembuskan napas dalam-dalam] Sial.
[Anton] Coming out, Don't shoot me, man!
[Anton] Keluar, Jangan tembak aku, Bung!
Coming out!
Segera keluar!
[Special Ops Officer] Let's see your hands!
[Petugas Operasi Khusus] Coba lihat tanganmu!
- Both, both hands! - [Anton] Okay!
- Keduanya, kedua tangan! - [Anton] Oke!
[Special Ops Officer] Get out and look at the building!
[Petugas Operasi Khusus] Keluar dan lihat gedungnya!
[garbled radio chatter]
[obrolan radio yang tidak jelas]
Keep coming, get on your knees!
Teruslah datang, berlututlah!
Up to your knees!
Sampai ke lutut!
[garbled radio chatter]
[obrolan radio yang tidak jelas]
[Shawn gime]
[Shawn Gime]
I'm so sorry about all this.
Saya turut berduka cita atas semua ini.
I know.
Aku tahu.
I can't believe I've been played so badly.
Aku tak percaya aku dipermainkan seburuk itu.
Well, it happens to all of us.
Ya, itu terjadi pada kita semua.
Hmm, since dad left, you're all I have.
Hmm, semenjak ayah pergi, hanya kaulah yang kumiliki.
You mean the world to me.
Kamu berarti segalanya bagiku.
I hated seeing you so depressed.
Aku benci melihatmu begitu tertekan.
This is the most alive I've seen you in a long time.
Ini adalah saat paling hidup yang pernah kulihat darimu selama ini.
- I love you bro. - I love you too.
- Aku cinta kamu, Sobat. - Aku juga cinta kamu.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Okay everything is okay, take care.
Oke semuanya baik-baik saja, jaga diri.
- Can you hear me? - [Shawn] Mm-hmm.
- Bisakah kau mendengarku? - [Shawn] Mm-hmm.
I'll see you on the other side.
Sampai jumpa di sisi yang lain.
[Shawn] Coming out!
[Shawn] Keluar!
- Coming out! - Both hands!
- Keluar! - Kedua tangan!
Both hands, both!
Kedua tangan, keduanya!
Both hands!
Kedua tangan!
Turn around and look at the building!
Berbaliklah dan lihatlah bangunan itu!
Do it now!
Lakukan sekarang!
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Come back to the sound of my voice!
Kembalilah pada suaraku!
Keep walking!
Terus berjalan!
Take two steps to your right!
Ambil dua langkah ke kanan!
Keep it coming, keep it coming!
Teruskan, teruskan!
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Stop, get on your knees!
Berhenti, berlututlah!
Don't move! Cuff him!
Jangan bergerak! Borgol dia!
Link.
Link.
Now it's just you and me. What time is it?
Sekarang hanya ada kamu dan aku. Jam berapa sekarang?
Three minutes.
Tiga menit.
You got it.
Kamu berhasil.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
[Shawn] Fuck this, dude.
[Shawn] Persetan dengan ini, kawan.
Where is Mason?
Dimana Mason?
He's in, he's the last one out.
Dia masuk, dia orang terakhir yang keluar.
[suspense music]
[musik menegangkan]
Enough of this shit! Let's go inside!
Sudah cukup omong kosong ini! Ayo masuk!
Let's go in! Come on!
Ayo masuk! Ayo!
[See! See! intense rock music]
[Lihat! Lihat! Musik rock yang intens]
♪ It's time to play ♪
♪ Saatnya bermain ♪
[the container is blocked]
[kontainernya diblokir]
[intense rock music]
[musik rock yang intens]
♪ Let's go in ♪
♪ Ayo masuk ♪
♪ Time to play, start your game ♪
♪ Saatnya bermain, mulai permainanmu ♪
♪ Full Metal Jacket ♪
♪ Jaket Metal Penuh ♪
♪ Bring the flavor like it's A1 ♪
♪ Hadirkan cita rasa seperti A1 ♪
♪ Fly with the flame lit ♪
♪ Terbang dengan api yang menyala ♪
♪ Flame lit, faithful to the game since day one, game on fire ♪
♪ Api menyala, setia pada permainan sejak hari pertama, permainan terus membara ♪
♪ Faithful to the game since day one, continued playing ♪
♪ Setia pada permainan sejak hari pertama, terus bermain ♪
♪ Keep it real 'til we die ♪
♪ Tetaplah nyata sampai kita mati ♪
♪ Yes, the game is on ♪
♪ Ya, permainannya dimulai ♪
[Special Ops Officer] Move Move!
[Petugas Operasi Khusus] Ayo Ayo!
♪ First things first ♪
♪ Hal pertama yang terpenting ♪
♪ Don't stop the beast on the clock ♪
♪ Jangan hentikan binatang buas di jam ♪
♪ Peace on the block ♪
♪ Perdamaian di blok ♪
♪ Respect is blocked ♪
♪ Rasa hormat terhalang ♪
♪ Look at me when you see me ♪
♪ Lihatlah aku saat kau melihatku ♪
♪ Reach the top ♪
♪ Capai puncak ♪
♪ Catching bodies along the way, each one outlined in chalk ♪
♪ Menangkap mayat-mayat di sepanjang jalan, masing-masing digariskan dengan kapur ♪
♪ Every day another crime scene ♪
♪ Setiap hari ada TKP baru ♪
♪ Even in the dark I still see you with the lights on high ♪
♪ Bahkan dalam kegelapan aku masih melihatmu dengan lampu menyala terang ♪
♪ Game on, by my side ♪
♪ Permainan dimulai, di sampingku ♪
♪ Everyone around me ♪
♪ Semua orang di sekitarku ♪
♪ We like to get loud ♪
♪ Kami suka bersuara keras ♪
♪ Leave it, then we go out here ♪
♪ Biarkan saja, lalu kita pergi ke sini ♪
♪ Every city, every state, a burning flame ♪
♪ Setiap kota, setiap negara bagian, adalah api yang menyala-nyala ♪
♪ Representing every county, every city, every state ♪
♪ Mewakili setiap daerah, setiap kota, setiap negara bagian ♪
♪ I have nothing against myself ♪
♪ Aku tidak punya apa pun terhadap diriku sendiri ♪
♪ It's gonna be faster, I'm faster, I'm faster ♪
♪ Ini akan lebih cepat, aku lebih cepat, aku lebih cepat ♪
♪ Then I bring the rapture ♪
♪ Lalu aku membawa kegembiraan ♪
♪ The capture for 100 thousand dollars ♪
♪ Penangkapan seharga 100 ribu dolar ♪
♪ I am the master of this tool ♪
♪ Akulah penguasa alat ini ♪
♪ Like a one man band ♪
♪ Seperti band satu orang ♪
♪ Wrapping that cash in a rubber band ♪
♪ Membungkus uang itu dengan karet gelang ♪
♪ Did I start the game? ♪
♪ Apakah aku yang memulai permainannya? ♪
♪ I'm going hard, it's on fire ♪
♪ Aku berusaha keras, itu membara ♪
♪ Full Metal Jacket ♪
♪ Jaket Metal Penuh ♪
♪ Bring the flavor like it's A1 ♪
♪ Hadirkan cita rasa seperti A1 ♪
♪ Fly with the A, all of you ♪
♪ Terbang bersama A, kalian semua ♪
♪ Flame lit, faithful to the game since day one, game on fire ♪
♪ Api menyala, setia pada permainan sejak hari pertama, permainan terus membara ♪
[Special Ops Officer] Ready, fire to the hole!
[Petugas Operasi Khusus] Siap, tembak ke sasaran!
[explosive explosions]
[ledakan yang eksplosif]
Of course!
Tentu saja!
♪ Since day one, I play ♪
♪ Sejak hari pertama, aku bermain ♪
♪ Keep it real 'til we die ♪
♪ Tetaplah nyata sampai kita mati ♪
♪ Yes, the game is on ♪
♪ Ya, permainannya dimulai ♪
[door knocking]
[mengetuk pintu]
[Official] Quick, quick.
[Resmi] Cepat, cepat.
- What do you mean empty? - [radio static hissing]
- Apa maksudmu kosong? - [suara radio statis mendesis]
[Officer 2] There's no one here, sir.
[Petugas 2] Tidak ada seorang pun di sini, Tuan.
- We've cleared all the rooms. - [inhales sharply]
- Kami sudah membersihkan semua ruangan. - [menarik napas dalam-dalam]
There are two missing targets.
Ada dua target yang hilang.
Find them!
Temukan mereka!
[dramatic music]
[musik dramatis]
Oops, you caught me.
Ups, kamu menangkapku.
Get on the ground!
Turun ke tanah!
Oh, no.
Oh, tidak.
I need to speak to Mr. Flowers.
Saya perlu bicara dengan Tuan Flowers.
This is your last warning.
Ini peringatan terakhir Anda.
And this one is yours.
Dan ini milikmu.
[explosions]
[ledakan]
[people shouting]
[orang-orang berteriak]
[Official] Back, back up.
[Resmi] Mundur, mundur.
- [people screaming] - [Hector] Fuck, was that it?
- [Orang-orang berteriak] - [Hector] Sial, hanya itu saja?
[Anton] The place blew up, man. Is the boss still there?
[Anton] Tempat itu hancur, kawan. Apakah bosnya masih di sana?
[parents in car crying]
[orang tua menangis di dalam mobil]
[confused people screaming]
[orang-orang yang kebingungan berteriak]
[soft, tense music]
[musik lembut dan tegang]
[Decker] I'm sorry about Mason.
[Decker] Aku turut berduka cita atas apa yang terjadi pada Mason.
[Amy] Me too.
[Amy] Aku juga.
You should have told me.
Kau seharusnya memberitahuku.
[Decker] You know the job.
[Decker] Kau tahu pekerjaan itu.
Well, you called me here for a reason.
Ya, ada alasan kau memanggilku ke sini.
The box of dirt, they never found it.
Kotak berisi tanah, mereka tidak pernah menemukannya.
Mmm.
Hmm.
Then there are the bodies. Never found either.
Lalu ada mayat-mayat. Keduanya tidak pernah ditemukan.
His brother Shawn, Anton and Hector
Saudaranya Shawn, Anton dan Hector
they can't seem to find them in the system.
mereka tampaknya tidak dapat menemukannya dalam sistem.
They simply disappeared from the network.
Mereka menghilang begitu saja dari jaringan.
Is there something you're not telling me?
Apakah ada sesuatu yang tidak kau ceritakan padaku?
♪ You said, "Sing me a song and sing it loud" ♪
♪ Kamu berkata, "Nyanyikan aku sebuah lagu dan nyanyikan dengan keras" ♪
♪ Put on a dress and let me take it off." ♪
♪ Kenakan gaun dan biarkan aku melepasnya." ♪
♪ Another pose for the room ♪
♪ Pose lain untuk ruangan itu ♪
♪ You said, "Make me a cake and leave it out" ♪
♪ Kamu bilang, "Buatkan aku kue dan tinggalkan saja" ♪
♪ Take me in your Cadillac" ♪
♪ Bawa aku dengan Cadillac-mu" ♪
♪ Another pose for the road ♪
♪ Pose lain untuk jalan ♪
♪ Now I wonder how ♪
♪ Sekarang aku bertanya-tanya bagaimana ♪
♪ Find time to please yourself ♪
♪ Temukan waktu untuk menyenangkan diri sendiri ♪
♪ Are we too far from love? ♪
♪ Apakah kita terlalu jauh dari cinta? ♪
♪ Will soul ever be enough? ♪
♪ Akankah jiwa cukup? ♪
♪ Will it ever be real enough? ♪
♪ Akankah itu menjadi kenyataan? ♪
♪ Will it ever be enough for you, baby? ♪
♪ Apakah itu akan pernah cukup untukmu, sayang? ♪
[Amy] Nice place.
[Amy] Tempat yang bagus.
Thanks. Would you like a beer?
Terima kasih. Anda mau bir?
I love one.
Aku suka satu.
Mmm.
Hmm.
How long are you going to keep me in suspense?
Berapa lama kau akan membuatku penasaran?
What do you want to know?
Apa yang ingin Anda ketahui?
My God, I don't know.
Ya Tuhan, saya tidak tahu.
Maybe... the part where you died.
Mungkin... bagian di mana kamu meninggal.
- Bueno. - [Amy] Mmm.
- Baik. - [Amy] Hmm.
Ah.
Ah.
[laughs] Wow.
[tertawa] Wow.
Mr. Flores.
Tuan Flores.
I love the name.
Saya suka nama itu.
Okay, you know how this works.
Oke, Anda tahu cara kerjanya.
You have to comply with our
Anda harus mematuhi peraturan kami
demands or the entire content of that
tuntutan atau seluruh isi dari itu
hard drive will be freed up immediately.
hard drive akan segera dibebaskan.
It doesn't matter if we are dead or in jail.
Tidak masalah apakah kita mati atau di penjara.
The same thing.
Hal yang sama.
- What are your demands? - Okay, fine.
- Apa tuntutanmu? - Baiklah.
The first is that I want my crew released immediately.
Yang pertama, saya ingin kru saya segera dibebaskan.
Um, I want identities for all of us, new ones.
Um, saya ingin identitas untuk kita semua, yang baru.
And $10 million in each of our accounts.
Dan $10 juta di setiap akun kami.
I'll give you those details.
Saya akan memberikan rinciannya kepada Anda.
One million dollars for Mr. Caras and
Satu juta dolar untuk Tuan Caras dan
maybe 1 million for each of the hostages.
mungkin 1 juta untuk setiap sandera.
That's all.
Itu saja.
What is our guarantee that the trash box will remain buried?
Apa jaminan kami bahwa kotak sampah akan tetap terkubur?
Oh, uh, [scoffs] at my word.
Oh, uh, [mengejek] pada kata-kataku.
You have no choice.
Anda tidak punya pilihan.
[Mr. Flowers sighs]
[Tuan Bunga mendesah]
Ah, good man.
Ah, orang baik.
How should we proceed?
Bagaimana sebaiknya kita melanjutkan?
Well, I think first
Baiklah, menurutku pertama-tama
we should blow up that C4 and pretend
kita harus meledakkan C4 itu dan berpura-pura
our deaths and continue from there.
kematian kita dan berlanjut dari sana.
[sighs]
[menghela napas]
Wow.
Wow.
And I thought he was ruthless.
Dan saya pikir dia kejam.
Well, the guy has to do his job.
Ya, orang itu harus melakukan pekerjaannya.
So where does that leave us?
Jadi, bagaimana dengan kita?
From the beginning.
Dari awal.
Look, I told you I would come.
Lihat, sudah kubilang aku akan datang.
[Amy laughs]
[Amy tertawa]
Hi Shawn. Nice to see you.
Hai Shawn. Senang bertemu denganmu.
Hola, Amy.
Halo, Amy.
Yes, Shawn, Shawn bought the property next door.
Ya, Shawn, Shawn membeli properti di sebelahnya.
I'm working on my swimming.
Aku sedang berlatih renang.
Yeah, I... I can see that.
Ya, aku... aku bisa melihatnya.
- Do you want to join me? - Well, maybe later.
- Kamu mau ikut denganku? - Mungkin nanti.
[Mason laughs]
[Mason tertawa]
Isn't it funny that the best score of all time
Bukankah lucu bahwa skor terbaik sepanjang masa
was the result of my younger brother's incompetence?
apakah ini akibat ketidakmampuan adikku?
I think it's perfect.
Menurutku, itu sempurna.
Me too.
Saya juga.
[Amy laughs]
[Amy tertawa]
Do you know what this place needs?
Tahukah Anda apa yang dibutuhkan tempat ini?
A garden.
Sebuah taman.
Oh yes, honey, with strawberries.
Oh ya, sayang, dengan stroberi.
Yeah.
Ya.
Dear.
Sayang.
[Amy laughs]
[Amy tertawa]
♪ You move like midnight ♪
♪ Kau bergerak seperti tengah malam ♪
♪ Slow, steady, slow ♪
♪ Lambat, mantap, lambat ♪
♪ Somewhere in the moonlight ♪
♪ Di suatu tempat di bawah sinar bulan ♪
If you like the subtitle give me a like and subscribe to Youtube - EasyTechOficial -
Jika Anda menyukai subtitle ini, berikan saya like dan berlangganan Youtube - EasyTechOficial -
[Jumbled lyrics]
[Lirik campur aduk]
♪ To take your soul ♪
♪ Untuk mengambil jiwamu ♪
♪ And rise higher ♪
♪ Dan bangkit lebih tinggi ♪
♪ Then you can go ♪
♪ Kalau begitu kamu bisa pergi ♪
[Jumbled lyrics]
[Lirik campur aduk]
♪ And what you say ♪
♪ Dan apa yang kau katakan ♪
♪ And take everything ♪
♪ Dan ambil semuanya ♪
♪ Live for deception ♪
♪ Hidup untuk tipu daya ♪
♪ Twisting every truth ♪
♪ Memutarbalikkan setiap kebenaran ♪
♪ Hide from the light of day ♪
♪ Bersembunyi dari cahaya siang ♪
♪ Marking every movement ♪
♪ Menandai setiap gerakan ♪
♪ You can glimpse the shadow ♪
♪ Kau bisa melihat bayangannya ♪
♪ It just fades away ♪
♪ Itu hanya memudar ♪
♪ Are you a good villain? ♪
♪ Apakah kamu penjahat yang baik? ♪
♪ I have a million ways to make you mad ♪
♪ Aku punya sejuta cara untuk membuatmu marah ♪
♪Tell me, are you a good villain? ♪
♪Katakan padaku, apakah kamu penjahat yang baik? ♪
♪ You're under fire ♪
♪ Kamu sedang diserang ♪
♪ To take your soul ♪
♪ Untuk mengambil jiwamu ♪
♪ And rise higher, then you can go ♪
♪ Dan bangkitlah lebih tinggi, maka kau bisa pergi ♪
♪ And get drunk ♪
♪ Dan mabuk ♪
♪ And what you say ♪
♪ Dan apa yang kau katakan ♪
♪ And take everything ♪
♪ Dan ambil semuanya ♪
♪ Guau, guau ♪
♪ Jambu biji, jambu biji ♪
♪ He's a good villain, I got a one man list ♪
♪ Dia penjahat yang baik, aku punya daftar satu orang ♪
♪ So that there are three ♪
♪ Sehingga ada tiga ♪
♪ Said he was a good villain, I got a one man list ♪
♪ Dia bilang dia penjahat yang baik, aku punya daftar satu orang ♪
♪ So that there are four ♪
♪ Jadi ada empat ♪
♪ You're under fire ♪
♪ Kamu sedang diserang ♪
♪ To take your soul ♪
♪ Untuk mengambil jiwamu ♪
♪ And rise higher, then you can go ♪
♪ Dan bangkitlah lebih tinggi, maka kau bisa pergi ♪
♪ And get drunk ♪
♪ Dan mabuk ♪
♪ And what you say ♪
♪ Dan apa yang kau katakan ♪
♪ And take everything ♪
♪ Dan ambil semuanya ♪
♪ Oh, and make you drive ♪
♪ Oh, dan membuatmu mengemudi ♪
♪ And watch you sleep ♪
♪ Dan melihatmu tidur ♪
♪ And take everything ♪
♪ Dan ambil semuanya ♪
[music stops]
[musik berhenti]
[Soft instrumental music plays]
[Musik instrumental lembut dimainkan]